YEAR 2000, ANTARCTICA
You mean the super solenoid theory
that Dr. Katsuragi proposed?
That theory is just too radical!
It’s nothing more than a hypothesis
at this point.
But only the S2 theory can explain
that giant’s power.
Mr. Ikari and his team are apparently
leaving on the 11th.
I wish they’d set up the smoking
area a bit closer.
We don’t even need to measure it
to know it’s true.
I heard there was talk of making the
entire facility smoke-free.
In fact, it existed in our reality,
You should be glad there is one.
So we have no choice but to acknowledge it.
If they’d done that, I wouldn’t be here.
I’ll accept it when all the data’s been verified.
Scientists put too much faith
in their own ideas.
What about the Lance of Longinus?
They’re a self-righteous kind.
It’s been sitting there
They become fixated too easily.
since it was shipped here last week
from the Dead Sea.
They’re incapable of accurately
assessing reality.
It will be treated before it’s sent
underground, won’t it?
And they are the ones seeking
to find the truth.
Are we okay on that?
The contact experiment with the donor
It’s quite ironic.
is scheduled for the 13th of next month.
They are not so noble.
We’ll be able to make the
adjustments in time.
Discovery is joy and understanding
is dominance.
Today’s experiment is on the ego threshold
signal of that field, was it?
All they seek is self-gratification.
Suppress the surface radiation!
It’s over the projected limit!
Emergency situation! Emergency situation!
The DNA that was inserted into Adam
is already physically fused!
All staff, get in your protective gear.
All workers in Level 2 and below,
immediately evacuate to the upper area
of Central Dogma.
All AT Fields are being released.
The Lance! Pull the Lance back!
It’s no good! We can’t maintain
the magnetic field!
It’s sinking in!
I don’t care if it only makes
a small difference!
Keep the damage to an absolute minimum!
The atomic components are breaking up
at the quark level! Hurry!
Begin thermal dampening treatment
as soon as the Door of Gaf opens.
I don’t care if it’s only for point one seconds!
Amazing! It’s begun to walk!
Get it to use up as much of its anti-AT
Field energy as possible!
The conversion system has already been set!
Countdown commencing!
It’s spreading its wings!
It’s breaking towards the surface!
Zankoku na tenshi no you ni
Just like the cruel angel
Shounen yo shinwa ni nare
Young boy, become a legend
Aoi kaze ga ima
Even though the untested breeze...
mune no doa o tataitemo
...taps at the door to your heart
Watashi dake o tada mitsumete hohoenderu anata
You just look solely at me and smile
Sotto fureru mono motomeru koto ni muchuu de
So intent on seeking out that gentle touch
Unmei sae mada shiranai itaike na hitomi
Such innocent eyes, still ignorant of their destiny
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday, you are sure to realize...
sono senaka ni wa
...that upon your back
Haruka mirai mezasu tame
You have the wings with which to fly...
no hane ga aru koto
...towards the distant future
Zankoku na tenshi no teeze
The cruel angel's thesis
Madobe kara yagate tobidatsu
Soon, you will take flight from the windowsill
Hotobashiru atsui patosu de
With your torrent of ardent pathos
Omoide o uragiru nara
If you are to betray our memories
Kono sora o daite kagayaku
You, who embrace these heavens and shine
Shounen yo shinwa ni nare
Young boy, become a legend
Hello, I’m not home right now.
Please leave your message after the beep.
My last job…
The red is as if it’s for the color of blood.
EPISODE 21
NERV IS BORN
Abducted?! The Vice Commander?
It happened two hours ago.
He was last seen in District 8 on the west side.
That’s within our compound!
What was your Intelligence Department doing?!
There’s an insider who leaked information
and instigated this.
He was able to get the better of us.
Someone who can pull the wool over
the eyes of Intelligence Division 2?
It can’t be!
Ryoji Kaji is the man believed to be
the mastermind behind this.
And that’s why you’re here.
We appreciate your quick understanding.
As a member of the same organization,
it is regrettable that we must suspect
the Chief of Operations,
but this is part of our job.
Considering the history between me and him,
it seems like the logical step to take.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Take her away.
It has been a while, Chairman Kiel.
This is quite a rude welcome.
I need not apologize to you for the impropriety.
This is a necessary procedure in order
to speak with you at leisure.
You certainly haven’t changed.
Does my convenience mean nothing then?
The problem being discussed
is an urgent matter.
It was unavoidable.
Please understand.
So, it’s Seele and not the Committee.
We have no intention of creating a new god.
We would like your cooperation,
Professor Fuyutsuki.
Professor Fuyutsuki…
Professor! Professor Fuyutsuki!
YEAR 1999, KYOTO
Oh, it’s you two.
You wanna join us for some beer in Kamogawa?
Again?
Ryoko and the others are saying
they’ll go if you go.
Our professor was also saying you should
show up once in a while.
Sure, all right.
It’s good to go out and have
a drink every so often.
Yes, Sir.
You excel at your work,
but you don’t take socializing seriously
and that’s not good.
I’m sure you’re right.
By the way, Fuyutsuki,
there’s a bioengineering student
who submitted an interesting paper.
The student’s name is Ikari. Do you know her?
Ikari? No, I don’t.
I told her about you and she said
she was interested in meeting you.
She’ll probably contact you eventually,
so take care of things, will you?
Ikari, was it? All right.
Metaphysical Biology Research Room 1 Fuyutsuki
I read your paper.
I found a couple of things questionable,
but it was a stimulating paper.
Thank you very much.
Yui Ikari, wasn’t it?
Yes.
What are your plans for the future?
Are you going to find work?
Or do you intend to join the research lab here?
I haven’t thought that far ahead yet.
And besides, aren’t you forgetting a third option?
I’m also considering a domestic life.
Of course, that’s only if I can find someone nice.
BACK IN THE YEAR 2015
With an S2 engine on board,
Evangelion Unit 01 has become
an absolute being!
We have no use for an actualized god.
We must not create a god.
We cannot allow that man to create a god.
Gendo Ikari, is he a man that can be trusted?
Gendo Rokubungi? I’ve heard of him.
BACK IN THE YEAR 1999
No, I’ve never met him,
Kyoto Prefecture Police Department
but there’s always some rumor
going around about him.
What? He asked to be released
into my custody?
No, I’ll come.
When should I come over there?
I heard about you from a certain person,
so I wanted to meet you.
You’re a rather coarse man,
to get into a drunken brawl.
There was no time to talk.
They just picked a fight with me.
I’m not very good at being liked,
but I am used to being treated coldly.
Well, it’s none of my business anyway.
Professor Fuyutsuki,
you seem to be exactly the person
I expected you to be.
Yes, my first impression of him was of distaste.
And back then, seasons and autumn
still existed in this country.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am seeing Mr. Rokubungi.
When I heard that, I wasn’t able
to hide my surprise.
I never would have thought you would
share your time with him.
Oh, but Professor Fuyutsuki,
he’s quite a sweet person.
It’s just that no one knows it.
Maybe it’s more blissful not to know.
Did I inconvenience you by
introducing you to him?
No, I’ll admit that he’s an interesting man,
though I can’t get to like him.
But within our circle, the common opinion
was that he had approached Yui
for her talent and for
the organization backing her.
Later, I would hear rumors that this
organization was called Seele.
YEAR 2000, ANTARCTICA
The Second Impact.
That tragedy occurred in the final year
of the 20th century.
YEAR 2001
And the first year of the 21st century
was pure hell.
There is no other word to describe that year.
YEAR 2002
RUINS OF TOYOHASHI CITY, AICHI PREFECTURE
I hear temperatures will rise above
30 degrees Celsius again today.
It certainly is hot over here.
That isn’t even rare in Japan these days.
Summer has lasted for almost a year now.
It’s rough on the body.
You don’t want to move to that ship up there?
You mean the next town over?
That place constantly stinks of oil.
I just can’t get to like it.
But still, I never imagined you’d
set up shop in such a place.
I had a lot of trouble finding you.
They’re short on doctors here,
like everywhere else.
It’s a mockery, but it’s better than nothing.
Going to Antarctica at this late date?!
It is a formal investigation of the incident
commissioned by the UN Council.
It is a provisional organization,
but I would think you could be of
more use to the world there,
than working as an unlicensed doctor here,
Professor Fuyutsuki.
That’s “former professor”.
By the way, my column is blank.
Who recommended me?
SAME YEAR, ANTARCTICA
To think this was once a continent of ice…
There’s no trace of it left.
Professor Fuyutsuki…
You?
I’m surprised you survived.
I’d heard that you were a member
of the Katsuragi Research Team.
Luckily, I had returned to Japan
the day before the incident,
so I was able to escape the tragedy.
I see.
Rokubungi, you…
Excuse me, I have a different name now.
A postcard? Not a business card?
We’re Married
Gendo & Yui
Ikari
It has been
a long time.
Are you doing well?
Ikari? Gendo Ikari…
My wife has been nagging me to get
this to you, Professor Fuyutsuki.
She seems to be a fan of yours.
I’m honored.
Gendo & Yui
Ikari
It has been
a long time.
Are you doing well?
How is Yui doing?
Isn’t she participating in this expedition?
Yui wanted to come, but we
have a child now, so…
SAFETY FIRST
Your organization… Seele, was it?
I’ve heard nothing but bad things about it.
I can’t approve of forcibly pinning down
the board of directors.
You’re fastidious as ever.
No clean organization can survive
in this day and age anymore.
The official investigation of the Second Impact…
If the investigation team consisted
only of Seele people,
you would run into all sorts of issues later.
We’re just a makeshift solution
to avoid that, aren’t we?
YEAR 2015
Nerv Headquarters - Isolation Facility 4
I still don’t handle dark places very well.
All the bad memories come flooding back.
Who is she?
She’s the sole survivor of the original expedition.
YEAR 2002
Her name is Misato Katsuragi.
SOUTH POLE INVESTIGATION SHIP - ISOLATION FACILITY 2
Katsuragi? She’s Dr. Katsuragi’s daughter?
Yes, she hasn’t spoken for
almost two years now.
That’s terrible.
It attests to the hell that she witnessed.
Her physical injuries have healed,
but psychological wounds do not heal so easily.
I suppose so.
We can’t conclude our findings for our
investigation lightly either.
A completely localized change to
the atmospheric elements.
The thorough extermination of all life,
including microorganisms.
The traces of an enormous cavern
directly below the blast center.
And this giant of light.
This incident is full of mysteries.
United Nations Moves Headquarters to Japan
In Five Years, Candidate is New Tokyo-2
Second Impact Caused by a Massive Meteor
Impossible to Predict or Avoid
Probability of Once in Every Several
Hundred Million Years
Official United Nations Statement
At 20-30% of the Speed of Light
Soon after, the United Nations issued
an official statement
stating that the Second lmpact was
caused by a massive meteor.
But from where I stood, I could see
that the information had been
blatantly massaged.
Behind all this was Seele and hints that
a man named Kiel was involved.
And it made me want to learn the
dark truth of that incident.
YEAR 2003, HAKONE
Even if that might eventually lead me
to the name of Yui Ikari.
UNITED NATIONS ARTIFICIAL EVOLUTION LABORATORY
It has been a long time.
Yes, it has.
DIRECTOR’S OFFICE
Why do you hide the existence
of the giant of light?!
You guys knew about the
Second Impact, didn’t you?
That it would happen on that day?
You said you were lucky enough
to get out the day before.
Was it also luck that you took
all your research with you?!
I am surprised that this material
escaped destruction.
I did a thorough investigation of your assets.
I’m sure raising a child is expensive,
but isn’t the amount rather large
for you to have privately?
You impress me, Professor Fuyutsuki.
Why not transfer to the department
of economics?
I’m going to go public about Seele
and the Dead Sea Scrolls
being secretly behind the Second Impact.
I have no intention of letting the people
who caused that get away with it!
Feel free.
But before you do, there is something
I would like to show you.
We’re going down quite a ways.
Does it worry you?
Somewhat.
What is this?
A cavern left behind by someone,
who was not us.
Though eighty-nine percent of it is buried.
An underground cavern that was originally
a neat spherical shape…
Is this the same as the underground
cavern found at the South Pole?!
The data from them are virtually identical.
Do you intend to repeat
that tragedy once again?!
Is that what you’re doing?!
Whether we are or not, please
determine that for yourself.
All the resources mankind has to offer
are being poured into that facility.
Oh, Professor Fuyutsuki.
Akagi, you too?
Yes, this is the best place to research
the fundamental theories for the
bio-computers of the future.
I see.
I intend to name it Magi.
Magi? After the three wise men from the East?
Is this what you wanted to show me?
No, this way, please.
Ritsuko, I’ll be right back.
What is this?
Is this that giant?!
Here at Gehirn, we call that giant Adam.
But this is not it.
It is not the original.
Then…
Yes, it is an Eva, made from Adam by man.
An Eva?!
This is the Adam Revival Project,
generally known as Project E,
and this is our mockup,
Eva Unit 00.
A prototype for a god?!
Fuyutsuki,
work with me to create a new era
in the history of mankind.
YEAR 2015
Excuse me, Ma’am?
Oh, I’m sorry. Let’s hurry up and retest Rei.
I haven’t seen Miss Katsuragi around today.
You’re right.
Miss Katsuragi?
Right! Misato Katsuragi! Nice to meet you!
YEAR 2005
NEW TOKYO-2, NAGANO PREFECTURE
Mother,
2ND TOKYO UNIVERSITY, SCHOOL GROUNDS
I met a girl named Katsuragi the other day.
Other people will only look at me from afar,
and each time, I am reminded of
the weight your name carries,
but this girl has no reservation
towards me for some reason.
I am told that she is the sole survivor
of that expedition.
She was apparently aphasic for a time,
but now, she chatters away a mile a minute
as if to make up for lost time.
Ritchan, I am still burrowed underground,
the same as always.
I’ve grown tired of the lunches they provide.
On the surface, they have apparently begun
working on the plans for New Tokyo-3
in accordance with the Second
Capital Transfer Project.
Lately, Misato hadn’t been showing up
at the university,
and when I finally got her to tell me why,
it was so idiotic.
Apparently, she had been sleeping with
her boyfriend at her apartment,
for an entire week!
I feel like I have seen an unexpected side of her.
She introduced him to me today.
He’s good-looking,
but I just cannot get to like his frivolous attitude.
As I recall, you have never been
good around boys, Ritchan.
In the end, being raised only by a woman…
No, I’m sorry. I have left you to your
own devices for so long.
It’s awful of me to act like a mother
only when it’s convenient.
A mother…
YEAR 2003
ASHINOKO LAKEFRONT, HAKONE
Today is just like every other day.
The disappearance of autumn
from this country is truly sad.
The secret Dead Sea Scrolls
that Seele possesses…
If things happen as it is written in those scrolls,
the Third Impact will happen in
another decade or so without fail.
The organizations are meant
to prevent the final tragedy.
That is what Seele and Gehirn are.
I support your ideas, not Seele’s.
Professor Fuyutsuki, it will be very dangerous
to unleash that seal upon the world.
I have already handed the data over to Ikari.
It’s not something that can be accomplished
by an individual after all.
There won’t be a repeat performance
of the stunt I pulled earlier.
And I’ve sort of received a warning.
Getting rid of me couldn’t be easier
for them, it seems.
The same goes for all the survivors.
It’s a simple thing to destroy people.
But that’s no reason for you to become
an experimental subject.
I will go along with the flow of things.
After all, that is why I am at Seele.
For Shinji.
YEAR 2004
HAKONE - UNDERGROUND LABORATORY 2
LCL electrified. Pressure at plus zero point two.
No destrudo readings detected in transmissions.
Para-base is stable.
What is this child doing here?
He’s Director Ikari’s son.
Ikari, this is not a nursery school.
Today is a crucial day!
I’m sorry, Professor Fuyutsuki.
I’m the one who brought him.
Yui, this is your experiment today.
That’s why.
I want to show my child the bright future.
Those were Ms. Yui’s final words.
The irregular circumstances erased her
from this world.
Exactly as I had wished.
I am such a horrible woman.
Ritchan, Director Ikari changed after that day.
Where have you been for the past week?
You’re allowed to grieve, but you
need to be aware
that you are responsible for
more than yourself now.
I know.
Fuyutsuki, I am going to recommend
a new project starting today.
I have already proposed it to Chairman Kiel.
You’re not going to…
That’s right.
The path to godhood that none have
ever succeeded in before.
The Human Instrumentality Project.
YEAR 2008
Mother,
congratulations on the completion of
the fundamental theory of Magi.
This is not exactly a gift to celebrate it with,
but my formal admission into Gehirn
has been unofficially approved.
I will be working on Project E
starting next month.
Who’s there?
Technology Development Department,
Ritsuko Akagi.
Here’s my ID.
I heard the command center
had been completed,
so I came to see it, but this place is a maze.
If you want the command center,
the Director and Dr. Akagi are there.
Are you really sure?
Yes, I have no regrets concerning my work.
Liar! You just can’t forget about Ms. Yui, right?
But I don’t mind.
YEAR 2010
GEOFRONT ARTIFICIAL CANOPY
LOWER LEVEL 2 DIRECT SUPPORT AREA (FUTURE LOCATION)
That’s the headquarters for Gehirn.
Good morning, Director.
Did you bring your child today?
Oh, but you have a son, if I’m not mistaken.
This isn’t Shinji.
I’m taking care of a friend’s daughter.
Her name is Rei Ayanami.
Hello, Rei.
This girl reminds me of someone…
Ms. Yui?
All files concerning Rei Ayanami
have been erased already?
It’s blank.
What does this mean?
COMPLETED
Magi Casper, Magi Balthasar,
and Magi Melchior.
The Magi are the three parts
that make up who I am.
The scientist in me, the mother in me,
and the woman in me.
And those three elements will be in
constant conflict with one another.
The three parts of you…
The only thing left is to power it up, right?
I’m going to go home early today.
Misato’s coming back.
That’s right, I didn’t know she
was a member of Gehirn.
I believe she’s in Germany?
Yes, she’s serving in Branch 3.
Then I suppose it’s a long-distance relationship.
I heard they broke up.
Oh, and they looked so good together too.
You can never tell with a man and a woman,
because it’s not logical.
That cool attitude of yours
certainly hasn’t changed.
You’re going to let your own
happiness slip away.
Happiness is even harder to define.
Well, it’s been a long time since
I’ve gone drinking.
Goodnight.
Did you want something, Rei?
I got lost.
Oh, really? Then you want to
leave here with me?
That’s okay.
But you won’t be able to get home
by yourself, right?
That’s none of your business, you old hag.
What?
I can go home by myself,
so leave me alone, you old hag.
It’s not nice to call someone an old hag.
But you are an old hag, aren’t you?
I’m going to get mad. You need
a good scolding from Director Ikari.
That’s what the Director calls you.
That…
He says, “That old hag is pushy,”
or that he, “doesn’t need that old hag anymore.”
He doesn’t need that old hag anymore.
It’s what the Director calls you.
You’re nothing but a…
It doesn’t matter if you die,
you can always be replaced.
Rei…
The same as me.
The Human Instrumentality Project Committee,
chaired by Kiel Lorenz,
dissolved the research organization,
Gehirn, the next day.
And they formed the special duty
organization, Nerv,
as the organization that would
carry out all projects.
All of us were moved directly into Nerv,
with the exception of one, Dr. Akagi,
the remarkable creator of the Magi System.
YEAR 2015
Now, I guess I’ll go.
Oh, it’s you.
Long time no see.
I’ve put the guards outside to sleep for a while.
This will cost you your life.
I just want to get closer to the truth
within myself.
Besides, it looks like they’ll find out
that I diverted the sample of
Adam to Commander Ikari,
so I have to guard my own interests too,
or various bad things will happen.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Is it over?
Yes, the problem has been resolved, so…
I see.
What about him?
I do not know.
Hey, you’re late.
I’m home.
Play
Messages
Katsuragi, it’s me.
I’ve probably put you through a lot of trouble
by the time you’re listening to this.
I’m sorry.
Tell Ritchan I said I’m sorry too.
Also, since I’ve troubled you so much anyway,
there’s this flower I’ve been growing…
It’d make me happy if you’d water it for me.
Shinji knows where it is.
Katsuragi, the truth is with you.
Go forward without any hesitation.
If I ever get to see you again,
I’ll say the words I wasn’t able
to say eight years ago.
Bye.
Message recorded at 12:02pm.
Jerk…
You’re really such a jerk…
Right then, all I could do was
run away from Misato.
There was nothing I could do or say.
I was a child.
It made me realize that.
TO BE CONTINUED
PREVIEW
The reality of having lost to Shinji corners
Asuka into a psychological pitfall.
The futility of panicking only produced
weariness and impatience.
Furthermore, the psychological attack
from an Angel
delivers the finishing blow to Asuka’s mind.
Asuka loses the means to recover.
The harsh reality tears apart people’s hearts.
Shinji is unable to offer her
any words of comfort.
Next time, “At Least, Be Human”
AT LEAST, BE HUMAN