"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawarujidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can'! buy my love name
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doom' n1' tada dakiai
Al' ga nai koto n1' k1' ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru ma: ni sakebou ze hol!
In the midnight dream
lki sue tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sue safety homo ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get moved!
Let': move into the brand new world
Let': dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mam aikyou
Kimeru toko duke no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji duke wa tooshi ikiteru
That': our law!
5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
Gog
Since I've been steering
hard and using the ABS,
the load on the front tires has
been a lot heavier than I thought!
This race is suddenly getting
much more challenging!
The five hairpins are coming up...
That's where he left you in the dust.
And I bet that's gonna be
a key point this time, too.
"Act 10:The 5 Consecutive Hairpins"
The Eight-Six is right on his tail!
I can't believe Nakazato is
having trouble with an Eight-Six!
There goes the Eight-Six': braking drift!
He': good!
--That was an FC!
--Ryosuke Takahashi...
I saw Keisuke Takahashi
lose the race on these five hairpin turns.
That Eight-Six turns comers using the gutter.
He's definitely not giving
up the inside position!
That's Nakazato.
What are you gonna do, Eight-Six'!
Wham'!
What?! From the outside?!
"Watch out!
--He's going to crash into us!
Don't insult me! Not from the outside!
The R32': acceleration is amazing!
What about that Eight-Six'!
He slid through that narrow turn.
Three more turns...
...and this race is over.
He's going outside again!
You're irritating me!
Stop messing with me from the outside!
The R32': movement is unsteady.
Nakazato is losing his patience.
--Yeah'!
"Watch, Keisuke.
The Eight-Six will make a move.
Make a move?
When there': no room on the inside...
...how can he pass?
Takumi': making a move?!
Are you serious?
--Come on!
--Go for it, Takumi!
This is humiliating. You keep
pushing me from the outside
in from of all these people!
I can't attack the comer because
I'm staying inside too much.
One car width should be enough
to keep him away from the inside.
That way, I can go in with more speed!
Good! He's going outside!
The Eight-Six is gone!
It can'! be!
What?!
Whoa...
wow,
Damn it! The understeer is acting up!
He faked going to the outside
and snuck inside while braking!
The Eight-Six can perform tricks like that?!
But the race isn't over yet.
I can still move ahead
in 2nd gear at full blast!
H! show you what my R32 is capable of!
I lost.
My R32 and I lost the race.
No... l lost the race.
My R32 didn't lose to that Eight-Six.
I never thought racers like that existed.
Losing was a shock...
...but somehow! feel satisfied,
because I gave it my best.
Dam...
Another 70,000 yen to fix this.
I'll train harder and try again.
Takumi won the race! He did it!
Guys, he did it!
--Takumi won the race!
--Yeah...
I can't believe it!
The Eight-Six passed the
R32 on the fourth hairpin!
How can an Eight-Six beat a R32'!
--That Eight-Six won'!
--| still can't believe it!
You were right, Bun ta.
You called it.
Wasn't that fun and educational, Keisuke'!
Yeah, that move the
Eight-Six used was amazing.
He faked going outside
and snuck inside while braking fully.
He must have great ABS.
You don't get it, do you, Keisuke'!
The Eight-Six doesn't come with ABS.
But...
That Eight-Six has human ABS.
Street racers who only drive cars with ABS
can't learn the strict pedal control
required to stop just before the brakes lock.
After all, ABS can't outperform the right foot
of a highly experienced driver like him.
It's been a while since I got that into a race.
That Eight-Six is a worthy target for us.
What are you staring at it for'!
Nothing...
Hey, Dad, this car...
What about it'!
Nothing... never mind.
I'm going to bed.
What'! How'!
I bought an Eight-Six!
I kept it a secret, but it came today!
It's relatively new.
You finally convinced your
dad to co-sign for you.
Well...
The guys at the shop were friendly,
and I think I got a great deal!
Yes!
It's in good shape.
You're lucky.
I can't believe you actually bought it, ltsuki.
I had to, Takumi.
I have to catch up with you, you know'!
I'll train hard to be your
"Downhill Eight-Six" partner.
I see your mouth got bigger.
I couldn't sleep last night...
...'cause I was so excited!
I know that feeling.
I couldn't sleep the night before I got my S13.
I couldn't help it, 'cause it's my own car.
My car... I feel like I'm dreaming...
'70s tires with original hubcaps...
So cool!
Why don't you start it up, ltsuki'!
Sure thing!
It doesn't sound too sharp...
It must be because of the original muffler.
Don't worry, I'll get a new muffler.
I want it to sound as cool as Takumi': Trueno.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Pop the hood, ltsuki.
--| knew it...
"Boss?
You got it all wrong, ltsuki.
What do you mean'!
--This isn't an Eight-Six.
"What?
It's an Eight-Five.
An Eight-Five... as in AE-85?
An Eight-Six and an Eight-Five
have the same body,
but their abilities are as far
apart as chalk is from cheese!
An Eight-Six has a DOHC engine,
while an Eight-Five has an SOHC.
DOHC and SOHC are
completely different, you know'!
Didn't you check the engine
before you bought it'!
Stupid!
Sorry, ltsuki, but it's funny...
My stomach hurts!
Itsuki, wait!
You went too far.
Put yourselves in his position.
We're sorry.
Itsuki!
Just leave me alone, okay'!
I can't.
I wanted to surprise you guys...
...but I was an idiot for buying a car by myself.
I knew it was too cheap for an Eight-Six.
I'm so embarrassed for acting
like an idiot in front of you guys.
I know you're laughing at me inside, too.
You're wrong.
The fact of the matter is, I envy you.
You envy me'!
Don't lie!
It's not a lie.
You're still in high school,
and already have your own car.
--My own car...
--Yeah.
So what if it's an Eight-Five'!
It has an engine and four tires.
It may not have power,
but it'll go fast downhill.
You can still practice your skills.
Cars are fun...
--You've changed...
--Have I'!
You weren't into cars as much before.
Takumi, I feel like I can
be proud of my Eight-Five.
--| don't deserve an Eight-Six yet.
--You're right.
You don't have to agree!
I may go for a spin at Mount Akina tonight.
Wanna come, Takumi'!
Sure... in your Eight-Five.
Takumi...
Yippee!
I'll come get you around 10:00 tonight.
--Sure.
--Don't fall asleep!
I didn't see the famous Eight-Six.
I wanna take a look at it.
I can't imagine an R32 losing to an Eight-Six.
"That's an Eight-Six.
--Is that him'!
Wow, that was fun! Akina Pass is the best!
It's slow going straight,
but it corners like the
real thing, right, Takumi'!
Sure.
What are you doing'!
If you look at my Levin from a distance...
...it does look handsome!
My Levin is so cool!
I'm glad I bought my Levin!
I'm happy for you, too.
--They're kids.
--It can't be them.
The famous racer who beat the R32
couldn't be a little kid!
No way!
How old are you kids'!
I hope you have a license.
Otherwise, I'll have to tell the police.
Yes, I do! I may look cute, but I'm 18.
Who do they think they are?
--Stop tormenting them.
--| don't like it.
A kid like him is driving an Eight-Six
and acting like a street racer.
You live around here'!
Do you happen to know the
famous Eight-Six of Mount Akina'!
Don't act dumb.We know you know him.
I, uh, I've heard of him...
...but he probably won't be here tonight.
Darn, we came all this way for nothing.
Let's get out of here.
I tell you what, kid.
If you wanna act like a racer,
at least try to look like one.
I mean, look at this
Eight-Six with its ugly wheels.
It's embarrassing!
Pitiful!
And change the muffler,
'cause it sounds pathetic.
Don't you know anything
at all about an Eight-Six'!
Well, actually...
...this is not an Eight-Six, it's an Eight-Five...
...so a new muffler won't make any difference.
I'm thinking of getting one, though...
An Eight-Five'!
No one carries new mufflers
for an Eight-Five anymore.
Nobody!
I'm crying!
I never thought anyone would be
driving an Eight-Five in this day and age!
It suits you well though, kid!
--Let's go.
--Thanks for the laugh, kid.
Don't let any scooters tailgate you!
That's it! They're gonna pay!
Itsuki, do you mind if I drive your car?!
But,Takumi!
Go to the passenger side. Hurry!
What are you gonna do, chase them'!
This is only an Eight-Five with
loose suspension and '70s tires.
It doesn't matter!
We don't have to do this, Takumi!
It doesn't have LSD, either!
Shut up and put on your seat belt!
It may get rough,
but just trust me, okay'!
I promise I won't crash your precious car.
Here we go!
Takumi! Ohh! Ohhh!
P... Please...
Take good care of my Eight-Five!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
Sou tanin wa kaizai shinai
Never stop, tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peak mezashite, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! Keikokuon wa so cheap!
Sheep-tachi wa michi wo akero
'Cuz Pm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy na motivation subete wa simulation
Nigetemitatte doko demo safety zone
Nani ka wo te ni irate nani ka wo wasureteku
Sakai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout, dare no te ni sue oenai
Hageshiiyumejikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream, yami o harisaite iku
Like a streak to the peak
Sekaijuu no kogekitta yoru o keshiteku
Rage your dream, michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
Konma zero-ichibyou de knockdown
Yoin nokoshikietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haishachi ni hau
Rikutsu duke no nougakitachi
Jamakusai kara shikato shitekou
Streaker satte yuku street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream, tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Al' mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream, ima o ikiteiru
--Are you crying, Mr. lketani?
"It's a cry of joy!
My $13 is finally coming back to me!
Oh, yes, that tragic $13
that crashed in Episode Two!
What': wrong, Mr. lketani?
By the way,I heard a red E66
was after Takumi': Eight-Six.
--Do you know anything about that?
--No.
Next on initial D, "Shingo Arrives!"
Don'! miss it!