"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let': look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let': go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
it': the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let': look for explosive thrills, it': the time!
"Act 5: Countdown to Destruction"
Akina': Eight-Six?!
Did you see that, big brother?!
Yeah. I guess...
...Kyoichi is scheming behind the scenes.
Can we let him race the Emperor?
There's no way he can pull it off this time!
This is street racing.
It's not up to us to decide
who gets to race whom.
But, big brother...
In the race I saw,
he totally exceeded my expectations.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I can't believe he's only 18.
Come on, now.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop" When I was 18,
I was far more capable than that.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
You may be the only one who thinks so.
Yuichi says your son is more talented than you.
He says you just don't want
to accept your son's talent
because you're so stubborn.
Anyway, when he exceeds his limits,
so will the engine.
Sooner or later, it'll blow.
Can he keep winning until then'!
Who knows'!
Here's the Eight-Six.
He took the bait as expected.
Thank you for showing up.
As promised, I'll be your opponent.
That's the least I can do for your trouble.
But I won't take it easy.
My courtesy to you is to give it my best.
His attitude is different.
He looks like a different person.
Let's go. We'll use the
"Handicap" method like before.
You go first.
The race starts after the first corner.
See you later. Call me if you need me.
Yeah.
Something': gonna happen tonight.
I have this uneasy feeling.
The Emperors came to rile up Takumi?!
They showed up here'!
I bet they really regret
losing to Takumi in Akina.
After all, they came to Gunma
planning to sweep the area.
What did Takumi say'!
He's not interested.
That's good.
He has no reason to go to Akagi
and battle it out with that monstrous Ian-Evo.
Yes.
Okay, I see.
This is weird.
What's wrong, ltsuki'!
Takumi isn't home.
He got a phone call, and then he just took off.
A phone call'!
I forgot to set my VCR to tape a show tonight,
so I wanted to ask him to tape it for me.
Did he take the car'!
I think so.
I know! He has a date!
With that girl.
Natsuki Magi'!
That's her. I'm positive.
I envy him.
If I had a cute girl like that,
I wouldn't be killing time here with you.
What are you saying, Kenji?!
We racers don't need girls!
"Right, lketani'!
"Right!
They're pathetic!
I want you to know that I
don't consider this a race.
I'm going to teach you the
difference between a fun car...
wand a fast car.
This is a seminar.
I'm ready.
There he goes!
Go get him, Kyoichi!
This is hard for me to comprehend.
He intentionally threw himself
into this unevenly matched race.
How can an obsolete Eight-Six
defeat Kyoichi': perfectly tuned Evo III?
And this isn't Akina, either.
Is that guy too stupid to realize that?
Does he trust his instincts
and experience that much?
I don'! understand what he': thinking.
Or does he believe he
actually has a chance to win?
Maybe he is...
...a racing genius in the making!
Unbelievable! They're really racing!
Watch me, Ryosuke.
4WD cars can'! lose to 2WD cars.
This race also serves as a
challenge sent out to you.
Watch out! He's swinging wide!
That Eight-Six is amazing!
He was just inches from
that vine-covered guardrail!
Is he insane?!
Even Akagi racers don't
attack that corner like that!
Big brother... the Evo lll's noisy
backfire didn't sound normal.
I noticed that, too.
That Evo Ill has the same system
that a WRC rally car has.
The misfiring system!
It's a good strategy by Kyoichi.
It's the best system imaginable
for a turbo car on a downhill course.
Akagi': slope is much more severe
than those ofAkina and Myogi.
Right after the start is a low-speed section
where they go straight down the hill
in a short amount of time.
Controlling the braking and steering
rather than abusing the power is the key.
He developed his technique
in the Gymkhana circuit,
so he's exceptional at slow corners.
He certainly has better technique now
than he did a year ago.
This new Kyoichi is a tough opponent.
The belief that 4WD cars can't tum is obsolete.
My Evo H! can tum!
I'm being hunted down... like helpless prey.
The Evo Ill sure is fast!
It even challenges the Eight-Six at the corners.
A better car or better skill'!
It's both! Sudo': cornering is unreal!
You know how Kyoichi Sudo races, right'!
What's his style?
He never makes mistakes.
He sticks with the basics
and avoids flashy moves.
In a race, he patiently tests
his opponent's weaknesses.
He will choose the most rational way to win.
He won't self-destruct, then.
He's different from Seiji.
Rationality is Kyoichi': bible.
That's why he's only interested in 4WD cars.
Against an equally skilled opponent,
he'll make sure his car
is better-equipped to win the race.
He's like that.
You sound rather bitter.
Idislike him.
I certainly don't want to lose to him.
That firing sound is so noisy!
I can'! stand it!
His adaptability is exceptional.
He has no prior experience on this course.
But he can still race at this pace.
What an unbelievable "downhill" sense.
But no more playing around.
H! end this shortly.
Thank you very much!
M091!
Takumi': girlfriend?
I got you something.
Thank you so much!
I'm haPPy-
Where is Takumi'!
His shift ended at 5:00 today.
You haven't seen him'!
No.
I thought you were with him.
There it is, my favorite cheesecake!
Bon appétit!
IfTakumi isn't on a date, where did he go'!
You said he took the Eight-Six, right'!
Yeah.
He may have taken the Emperors' bait
and gone to Akagi.
No way!
Takumi went to Akagi?
We're entering the flatter,
mid-speed section here.
Without a slope, he's as slow as a turtle.
The next "S" tum will do.
He can'! avoid my counterattack.
There!
No way!
This is a short, full-blast section.
What acceleration!
He': charging in from the outside.
Challenging the Eight-Six at a comer?!
He'll take the inside
position at the next comer.
And with that amazing acceleration...
...the Eight-Six is going down!
What?! The Evo Ill took the lead'!
At a corner'!
Yeah...
Yeah.
Yeah. I see.
Big brother?
It's just like Kyoichi.
He chose not to attack
at the steep-slope section.
He waited until the Eight-Six
lost speed on the flatter section.
With his technique and the Evo lll's abilities,
Kyoichi could've taken the lead earlier.
But he waited until he had
a surefire chance to pass.
That's the Kyoichi I know.
Will the Eight-Six have a
chance to regain the lead'!
Don't ask me that.
I know you can figure out the answer yourself.
Idiot!
He should've stayed home and let us handle it!
He didn't have to suffer this pointless loss!
He': following me...
ma! the same distance.
Amazing! He picked up more
speed after losing the lead.
Usually, the corner exit
is the key for a turbo car
while it's the corner entrance for an NA.
To put it simply, that's the
theory of downhill racing.
But with the misfiring system...
Right.The misfiring system makes
both the Turbo's torque and
the NA's response possible.
With Kyoichi': abilities,
that Evo Ill becomes a
monstrous cornering machine.
It can superbly enter and exit a corner.
It's perfect for a dogfight.
Like I said, this race was suicide!
From the get-go, this race
was never about speed.
What'!
Think about it.
Kyoichi has carefully studied this course,
while Takumi Fujiwara has no experience here.
There's no question who the favorite is.
Right.
I don't know what went on between them,
but Fujiwara showed up
without the tools to win this race.
But why did he have to be so irrational?
Only he understands that.
Sometimes we want t0 race
to blow off some frustration within us.
He had that air about him.
This isn't his normal racing style.
The Eight-Six's high-pitched
exhaust sounds like...
...an enraged roar.
Whenever I turned around
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
The warm wind
Comes back quietly and tenderly
And as I gaze at the sky alone
You smile down upon me
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory
Takumi gave up the lead.
Can he ever regain the lead, and...?
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"Goodbye Eight-Six."
Don'! miss it!