"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
in the silver smoke amidst the frozen city
Payback for a dream I've seen so many times
My body is frozen in a
memory that! can't shake
Slam on the accelerator and deceive myself
Broken in the night
My eyes become sharper
All from someone': whim
It seems like the world will end any minute
Break into the night, it': the time
With scared eyes, Pm lost in the night
Embraced by a falling dream
Scared of being alone, missin' my heart
Even hurting myself
Love me so much,
enough that! could fall apart
if only I could throw everything away
And just love you
Then I know! could face the truth
Pm going at full power,
and he's right on my tail!
No matter how fast I 90,! still can't get away!
It's no good.
I might lose this race!
Ryosuke Takahashi...
I can't even compare to such a great racer!
Pm going to lose!
"Act 26: The New Downhill Legend!"
I'm going to lose!
Amazing!
Pm getting goose bumps.
He': following such a perfect line.
If! weren't right behind him,
copying his every move,
it would have been almost
impossible for me to do this.
Beginners can drive fast on a straight line.
Intermediate drivers can master corners.
But truly advanced drivers
find their own course,
and that': how they get ahead.
To find that ultimate course
is the main objective of
my "fastest driver" theory.
I can'! believe I've found
the best example of my theory
on such an occasion, after
searching for it for so long.
What amazing talent.
--Here they come!
--Which one is it'!
Ryosuke Takahashi or the Eight-Six?!
Whoa!What intensity!
How impressive!
It': no good! I can'! widen the lead!
All right! They're coming!
Just the sound of it gives me shivers!
Since the straight section before
the five hairpins is quite long,
I bet there'll be some hard braking.
Here they come! The Eight-Six is in front!
RYOsukQQ!
Entrance to the five hairpins here.
I can see both cars now.
The Eight-Six is leading!
Wow, the Eight-Six?!
Too much speed. He messed it up.
Damn it! Tum!
He could have powered through it
and brought it back if he were
driving a more powerful car.
But how reckless to try it with an Eight-Six!
Ryosuke': FC took the lead!
What?!
When the Eight-Six over-accelerated
and under-steered, Ryosuke passed it!
The Eight-Six under-steered?
He's just amazing!
Ryosuke is in a class by himself!
Now I am totally sure that
Ryosuke is going to win!
Such a strange guy...
What an unexpected weakness!
I was planning to stay
behind him a little longer
so I could hide my strengths.
Now that Pm in from,I don'!
want him to get right behind me,
so before he recovers, I'd better widen the gap
and guarantee myself the win.
The FC just passed us.
The Eight-Six is a little behind.
Ryosuke': time is amazing!
He could beat the course record
by almost twelve seconds!
Twelve seconds?!
The race is over.
My brother will just widen the gap now.
Just hearing about it gives me chills.
Even if he loses, it won't
hurt Takumi': reputation.
It's just that Ryosuke Takahashi
is simply incomparable!
Wait a minute.The race isn't over yet!
I still believe that Takumi
can come back and win.
But...
He always has, hasn't he?!
No matter how bad it's looked,
he's always come back and won.
I am sure he can do it again!
Please get to the bottom safely!
Don'! do anything crazy, Takumi!
The merit of a light and compact
rotary engine is not the power,
but the agility you get from an
ideal front-back weight distribution.
I just love the consistent
spirit of the rotary engine.
Even if! have to put my pride on the line,
the rotary engine can'! fall behind
the Eight-Six on the comers!
Whoa!
Aren't Ryosuke Takahashi and Takumi great'!
The drift punks around here don't
even come close to that speed.
Sayuki, what's going to happen in this race'!
It's impossible to pass
Ryosuke once he's in front.
But it's Takumi he's racing against!
Takumi hasn't given up yet.
The lines he chooses are better than the FC's.
You can tell he's driven Akina Pass a lot.
I thought he would be way
ahead once he passed me!
I still have a chance!
Pm getting closer!
The gap is narrowing!
Shoot!
All of a sudden, my from tires
aren't sticking to the road.
Could it be heat wear?
Following and copying the Eight-Six': driving
might have put more strain on
the front tires than I expected.
The Eight-Six is getting closer...
Isn't he having any problems with his tires?
A little wear on the tires won't
affect my technique, though.
I can'! catch him like this.
I need to get closer all at once!
Dam it! is this my limit?
Should I try that thing?
The "other gutter driving" that
my dad talked about that time?
Oh, good job.
Hey, Dad. I think I found a good trick
to avoid skidding on a
curve in snowy weather.
You hook the tires on one side
into the gutter next to the road.
You can corner so easily, it's like a joke.
"Gutter driving," huh'!
I use that technique often, too.
Shoot.You use it too, huh?
Takumi. There are two ways to
use the gutters in Akina': roads.
The method you discovered is to
use the gutter as you enter the corner
so you can prevent under-steering.
There's another one.This one
emphasizes recovery after a corner.
The timing for getting both in
and out of the gutter is different.
It's pretty tough. Try and
figure it out for yourself.
I haven'! tried it yet.
It': a big gamble. Should I try it?
Okay. Here I go!
What did he just do?!
What the heck did he just do?!
It sounds like they're coming, Shingo.
Judging from the skidding sound,
they must be very close to each other.
Just as I expected!
This is the only spot where
they can go for the win.
The straightaway lets you
speed up for the braking to come.
Unlike the rest of the
narrow mountain pass road,
this corner has three lanes,
so you can choose your own line.
On top of that, this is a compound
corner where two R's overlap.
The finish line is right over there.
This has to be the point
where they go for the win.
The one who leads after this corner
is the one who wins the race!
Here they come!
Wow! The FC is in front!
The Eight-Six is right behind him!
What will they do?!
There's no way to pass from the outside!
Go inside!
Inside?! Or outside?!
Outside?!
Ryosuke didn't leave any room on the inside!
There was no way to go inside!
Whoa! The FC is in front!
The inside has the absolute advantage!
The FC is skidding to the outside
of the curve! Is this for real?!
He's going way too fast
to get out of the curve!
No way!
Their lines will cross!
Here they come!
Here they are!
No way!
I can't believe Ryosuke Takahashi is losing!
That's Ta ku m I's ca r!
Takumi...
It's the Eight-Six! The Eight-Six won!
I can't believe it! On top of that,
he set an amazing course record!
My big brother has lost.
The legend of the unbeatable man is over.
Banzai! Takumi won! The Eight-Six won!
Hooray!
Whoopee! He did it!
Banzai! Banzai!
Hey! Are you listening, Bunta?!
Takumi has won!
Don't get so excited. Of course
he won. That's no surprise.
He set an amazing course record, too!
Right, right. Okay, then. I'm hanging up.
That guy!
So he won...
That Takumi...
We've just seen one heck of a race.
I'm still in a state of shock.
Wow,
Hey, Shingo! Get farther away from me!
If someone sees us, they'll think we're friends.
You get away!
Takumi did it! He beat RyosukeTakahashi.
--That is so cool!
--Yeah.
Maybe I'll askTakumi out again!
What'!
Why don't you ask that guy out too, Make'!
What was his name'!
Let's see...
--lketani'!
--Right!That's him!
There's still a chance!
Let's go on a double date!
Um, there's one thing I want to ask...
Do you mind'!
How come you waited for me
to take charge in the race'!
You think I slowed down on purpose
in the last half of the race'! No way.
But then why...'!
You must have picked up your pace a notch.
I tried my best not to slow down,
but my front tires were acting strange.
--Tires'!
--But I can't use tires as an excuse...
Conditions were the same for
both of us, and I clearly lost.
I, uh...
I don't think that I'm a faster
driver, or anything like that.
You really are weird.
I've never met anyone like you before.
Don't be content with winning
on a small stage like Akina.
Turn your gaze towards
the bigger world out there.
Takumi Fujiwara... you were very fast.
See you around.
I open a window to the dawn sky
And your bare skin almost
liquid in the soft breeze
Gently I draw you to me, and with each kiss
Gently I draw you to me, and with each
kiss --It's autumn already. --Yeah.
My heart trembfes like I can hardly
believe --It's autumn already. --Yeah.
My heart tremble: like I can hardly believe
Shank! we head back, Takuml?!
Sure.
My heart tremble: like I can hardly believe
The passionate thrill brimming over within
This car is small but very fast.
Knocks on a rusty door
I think it's really cool. I like it after all.
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
I want to show you how
I feel with my whole body
Let me get drunk on
this love, miraculous flower
Let me get drunk on this Io ve,
miraculous ffo wer T...Takumi!!!
There was a time when I wandered
aimlessly, tired of Jove T...Takumi!!!
There was a time when I wandered aimlessly,
tired of Jove You've gotten another challenge!
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
You've gotten another challenge!
This time it's really bad. Oh, man!
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let': enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Here. Now get going.
In half a year or so,
We'll prove countless times...
I might become a better driver than you, Dad.
Our passion will last for eternity!
Nonsense.
I'm still better than a baby like you.
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
ever so strongly and vividly
I want to show you even more
how I feel with my whole body
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
wand miraculous flower
The big world out there...