"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Kikanaku natteta
ano CD wo mam sagasou
ltsushika nervous-gachi no futari no tame ni
Speed tozashita kako ga
mezamete iku melody
Chikyuu ga furueru hodo ni
kakushinhan no neraiuchi
Blazin' beat
Hui hodo tsuyoi ai wo abisete
Sakebu kaze hibiku oto de daite
Naked mind, desire
Motomeru koto ni tsumi wa naku
Utagau koto sum wasurete mi wo makasete
Blazin' beat! Yo! Binbin de ikou,
moral wa hashotte ii darou
Shoudo no mama ni tobidasou
Weekend da yo zenin shugo!
M.O.V.E., move, buchigiri hajikeru
Torihada mon no wakuwaku
wo sagasou, it's the time!
Pm sure Kama is right about this.
Fujiwara is racing another
Eight-Six at Shomaru Pass.
When I saw him that morning,
he still wasn't used to the new Eight-Six.
But a race is different.
The veil of secrecy around
the new engine is coming off.
"Act 12:
Eight-Six vs. Eight-Six: A Spirited Race"
"Act 12: Eight-Six vs. Eight-Six: A Spirited Race"
--Man, I just can't stay calm. --Me neither.
--Man, I just can't stay calm.
--Me neither.
But I have to work.
Maybe you can go and...
Boss.
Just go while I'm looking the other way.
Okay! Ready, Kenji?
Yeah.
If I were a little younger,
I would leave work to see it, too.
I'll be right there!
Come on, we're in a hurry!
Look, Kenji.
Isn't that Takumi': girl'!
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe she's looking for a part-time job.
"Seibu Chichibu Station"
What?!
'Z5232?
Why are you here'!
A let's happened since last night.
You're the one who chose this location.
Kazumi, you guys wait here.
But why?
You can catch a bus or a train
from here in the morning.
If anything should happen to our cars,
at least you won't be stuck here.
What?! Takumi!
Are you guys going to Shomaru Pass'!
You shouldn't race there!
--Pick another place!
--Be quiet, Kazumi.
Stay out of this.
--Big brother...
--Just so you know...
...the pass we're about to race
on is very narrow and tricky.
I'll take the lead first.
Since this is your first time,
we should take some precautions.
We'll alternate positions
and keep going until one pulls away
or passes the other.
It's a sudden death race.
If we're equally skilled,
another element will be the factor.
Another element'!
Luck, stamina,
compatibility with the car... that sort of thing.
Let's go.
When we get there,
I'll turn on my hazard lights
and we'll start.
Takumi!
Did Takumi know that
Kazumi would be here, too?
ls Shomaru Pass really that dangerous?
It's an old road.
It's not that long,
but you go uphill first,
then downhill from the middle.
It's half uphill, then.
That's not all.
It's narrow and has poor visibility,
which has resulted in many accidents.
The guardrails are all rusted.
The road': uneven and slippery.
Wataru has had two accidents there.
He said it was a tough pass to race.
What?!
This is Takumi': first time!
It's too risky!
His hazard lights! Here we go...
Ready? Don'! crash your precious car yet.
It': an uphill.
What?!
I told you so.
It's a great engine.
You can even stay with me on this hill.
No need to take it easy, then!
--Good night!
--Bye! Take care.
Pm sorry, Takumi.
Pm the one who': to blame.
I know that now,
but I don'! know what to do.
So for now, I'll try working
part-time like youffakumi.
Pm determined to change.
I drive an Eight-Six
because defeating an opponent
with this disadvantageous old car
is so satisfying.
But this time, it': different.
I absolutely can'! lose to another Eight-Six!
I've never felt this much
pressure in a race before!
I can see the aura that
radiates from your Trueno!
Is this a good spot, Keisuke'!
The course is so narrow that
there's no other place to watch from.
There!
Here we go!
That sudden boost of power is to die for!
The obsolete "boom" turbo.
Hey, Keisuke'!
Aren't Fujiwara': Trueno and Akiyama': Levin
basically the same car except for
their front and tail lamp designs?
--Yeah.
--Why do they run differently, then'!
Well, that's because...
I should have my brother explain it to you.
I understand it in my head,
but I'm not good at explaining.
Like Kenta said, the Trueno
and the Levin are like twins.
But since their engines take
different tuning methods,
they've become two completely different cars.
The method without the turbocharger
is called mechanical tuning.
Fujiwara': Trueno is that.
His foot on the gas pedal
controls the rpm directly.
Its instant response is its strength.
Even after entering a corner
at nearly top speed,
he can make further adjustments to his attack.
Unlike with a turbo,
he can attack corners aggressively.
Cars like his excel at entering corners.
In contrast, Akiyama': Levin is a turbo.
It may be a step slower at corners,
but its acceleration on
straightaway: covers that.
Cars with turbos excel
at coming out of corners.
How about the Levin's fishtailing, then'!
The "boom" turbo tends to lag,
so once the boost pressure goes down,
it takes time to get it back up.
That's why he keeps his foot
on the gas when exiting corners
and controls it using counter-steer only.
He probably mastered
that fishtailing technique
to deal with the peculiarities of his car.
Got it, Kenta'!
Pass racing is very complex.
Yes, I get it now.
What's up with that?!
Are you sure this is the place'!
Yeah, I guess so.
What's that'!
Takumi!
Wow! That's a "boom" turbo.
That car almost looks out of control.
He's barely staying on this narrow road.
But when he's on, he's super fast.
He's a different kind of opponent
who breaks all the conventional rules.
This is the second round.
From behind, H! be observing
your undefeated Gunma-grown talent.
This corner is hard to get through!
Right now, all the elements
are against Fujiwara.
It's a tricky course where
he has no experience,
and the Levin's irregular
pace breaks his rhythm.
But more than anything,
he has been feeling uneasy
with his new and unfamiliar Eight-Six.
That's his biggest handicap.
The bad condition of this road
is making my car shake!
The inner edge of the road is unusable!
If the tires catch it, they'll slip!
I can'! use the outer edge
coming out of comers, either.
There's less usable area on this
road than there appears to be.
Takumi...
The suspension settings change
based on the engine power.
After I installed the new engine,
you kept saying you couldn't corner like before,
which is logical.
The car was set up that way.
Only by revving up to a
high rpm will you be able
to comer at a higher speed.
Notice that, Takumi.
Unseal the car': capabilities.
What': this?
Did I imagine it?
The turbo is so fast that Pm kind of scared.
This car is nothing like it was before.
It needs more detailed maintenance.
And I have to watch the
gauges while I'm racing.
It costs money and takes effort,
but I have no regrets.
I've gained the power I was craving.
See, Kazumi...
...it's no good if you stop growing.
If you keep running away
from things you're bad at,
you'll never be good at anything.
You just have to keep searching
and moving forward on your own two feet.
Big brother...
Kazumi'!
Oh, thank you.
It's warm.
"Listen, ltsuki.
--Yeah'!
I don't think I'll be going back to Gunma.
So...
...I guess this is probably good-bye for us.
What?!
My parents found out about
my leaving work the other day
and are angry with me.
But that's not the reason.
I was thinking in the car.
I realized that I need to choose my own path.
Because only if I choose my own path
can I say to myself that I was right in the end.
My old job, and this temp job at the hotel,
weren't really my idea.
I'll find a job myself this time.
And I also have a small goal.
A scan
I'll save up and get my
driver's license, like you.
That'll be my first step towards independence.
I was wrong to think that
moving to another place
would solve my problems.
I want to hold the steering wheel
instead of sitting in the passenger seat.
I want to be able to run on my own,
without anyone': help.
Kazumi, I, uh...
I won't go back to Gunma,
because I can't get my license there.
Uh, I...
Thank you for everything, ltsuki.
I...
...have fallen in love with you, Kazumi.
The second round!
He's getting used to it.
What'!
It's time for the new Eight-Six to wake up.
It did get easier to control.
I was struggling with it just yesterday.
Is it because of this power?
I can control it.
All right.
I may just pull it off!
I was planning to just
observe him in this round,
but that won'! work.
He': adapting to this tricky
course at an amazing rate.
No other first-timer could race this fast here!
Pm impressed!
Racers like you do exist!
I can'! lose on my home turf!
This will be a tough race!
Make sure to rev up to 11,000 rpm.
Good pass racers are the coolest.
You're not bad.
Your sharp technique could convince anyone.
I can go for broke with my Levin!
I wanted excitement like this.
Pm the luckiest man alive!
At the end of the last round,
I was going full blast.
H! finish you in this round!
You're a great opponent.
You've set my spirit on fire!
Furikaereba itsudatte
Kawaranu kimi no egao ga aim
Arukitsukare tachidomaru hi mo
Chiisa nu yorokobi no hi mo
Kono ryoute ni kakaekirenai
Al' wo oshiete kureta
Atatakaku
Sotto yasashiku yomigaeru kaze wa
{ma hitori sora wo
Mitsumeteru boku ni hohoendeiru
Mada ano hi no mama no
Mabushisa de te wo futteiru
Kimi wa everlasting memory
Each with their own hopes...
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
The last episode: "Changing Seasons."
Don'! miss it!