"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let': look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let': go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
it': the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let': look for explosive thrills, it': the time!
They're coming into the first corner.
The Evo IV is following?!
No matter how well you tum comers...
...you're just an Eight-Six.
Anyone driving a junker like
an Eight-Six is beneath me!
I wouldn't race them even if they asked.
But the car...
I'd have to say the Eight-Six
is no longer good enough.
We will never lose.
The king of mountain passes is the Len-Eve!
No one knows who will win
until we actually race!
"Act 3: Premonition of Defeat"
With the speed of the Evo IV,
Seiji should take the lead
before the first corner, despite his late start.
That wasn't even Seiji': full start, though.
He stayed behind on purpose?
L5 he o u .
n Simulation 2-,,
Offensive-minded Seiji is being very careful.
No need for that against an Eight-Six.
"Simulation 1" should be enough to beat him.
Not necessarily.
Seiji is a top-notch racer, but he': not clever.
So far, all his races were easy,
so he's getting careless.
"Simulation 3" is to tighten his loose mind.
Don'! fail me, Seiji.
Stumbling here before facing Ryosuke...
...is unacceptable.
Maybe it's too much to ask.
Basically, the Evo IV is a WRC rally car.
It's light, and is equipped with turbo and 4WD.
On top of that, the driver
has first-class technique.
Takumi can't win.
Come on, lketani and Kenji!
Why are you always so
pessimistic about things?
But, ltsuki...
It's Takumi who is racing!
Unlike others,
Takumi always makes
something happen when he races.
Damn, I don't like this.
This is irritating. Damn it!
Hey, Papa'!
I, uh...
I don't think I should see you anymore.
That's sudden. Can you tell me why'!
There's someone I like now.
I mean, I like you, too, Papa.
But this is a different kind of liking.
Sorry I'm so selfish.
This is a joke.
Why does my Evo lV have to stay cooped up
behind this ancient Eight-Six?
I can barely step on the gas.
Pm getting frustrated.
"Full Blast" is all that': in my Evo lV dictionary.
Why use "Simulation 3" against this old junker?!
He': nowhere near that good, Kyoichi!
Don'! be impatient, Seiji.
What': this anger? Pm irritated!
Why am I so irritated?!
Hey, Keisuke'!
What did Ryosuke say about this race'!
He didn't say much.
He only told me to be at this
spot if I wanted to watch.
It sounds like there's a reason behind that.
Yeah.
It's common sense that the
Eight-Six can't win this battle.
He's racing a Ian-Evo, after all.
Don't act like you know everything, Kenta.
Isn't it also common sense that your S14
shouldn't be slower than an Eight-Six'!
Don't torment him, Keisuke.
The race against the Eight-Six
turned out to be a great experience for Kenta.
Yeah, what do I care'!
"Emperor" or whatever they're called,
one thing will be certain after this battle
against Takumi Fujiwara on Akina's downhill.
This is the longest straightaway on this course.
I can easily get ahead of him if I want.
If you get impatient and jump ahead, it's over.
Damn it! I've had enough of this!
That's how everyone lost,
including my brother.
If you jump ahead, you lose'!
Right. Can you understand
that paradox, Kenta'!
Here I go!
"Simulation 3" or not, Kyoichi...
...I just have to win this race, right?!
He': fast.
Now you'll see how outclassed you are.
Hljust keep blasting away
until you disappear from my rearview mirror.
See ya, Eight-Six!
"Mt. Akina Forest Park Skate Center"
Would you please reconsider?
You really make my life worth living.
I really don't mind if you have a boyfriend,
as long as we stay the same.
I know, I can give you more gifts.
Papa, 51°!'-
It's not that.
I've always liked you, Papa.
Despite our age difference,
I thought it was normal to have
a relationship with the person I liked, but...
...now that I think about it,
that's why you were giving me gifts.
This can't be normal.
Do you really like this boy...
...that much'!
I probably do.
Right now, that's all I can say.
What'! Seiji got ahead of the Eight-Six?!
--He's pulling away!
--All right!
I knew it.
That's the Seiji we know. He's gone now!
--That Eight-Six is nothing!
--Yeah!
Despite his looks, Seiji is highly skilled.
He won't lose now.
Idiot!
Seiji has mastered driving his Ian-Evo fast.
He knows that a 4WD car has to enter a comer
at top speed to be able to drift through it.
During the drift, you can only control the car
by steering while flooring the gas pedal.
The car tends to fishtail if you try to control it
with the pedal like you would an FR.
Full acceleration is the 4WD': way.
That': the hardest thing
about driving a 4WD car.
No mediocre racer can tum with full control.
But once you master the technique,
you can turn any corner
at remarkably high speed.
I guess I don'! have to worry about Seiji, but...
...why am I feeling so anxious?
Enter with speed and tum with full acceleration.
It': completely different from
the junker FR': slow "crab" tum.
Watch me and learn.
Of course, he has to be close by to see it.
I doubt he': anywhere near me.
He': so far...
What?!
He': right behind me instead of far back!
That': impossible!
He can keep up with my drift?
He': better than I thought. I see.
I get it now.
My irritation didn't come
from not being able to
speed up on the straightaways.
I guess I was aware of the actual reason
while I was following him.
I hate to admit it, but I... I...
Pm slower at comers!
So far, I've managed to keep up with him.
There': one more thing.
The straightaway: are shorter around here,
and the difference in power
doesn't matter much.
But just wait.
In the upcoming high-speed section,
H! erase you from my rearview mirror.
I bet my Ian-Evo racer': pride on it!
At the end of a long,
accelerating straightaway
waits a hairpin tum.
That': how it is.
Here it comes.
H! outrace you with my technique,
not my machine': capabilities.
He's fast. He certainly is!
That's a very fast car.
They'll be here shortly.
Here they come!
The Ian-Evo is ahead. He's charging in!
Akina': famous five hairpin turns.
What power!
It's like a WRC car.
The Eight-Six is way behind.
I've never seen him this far behind
at the five hairpins in past races.
Maybe the Eight-Six can't pull it off this time.
That car is too inferior.
There!
It': time to use the ditch!
That was fast.
How did he turn so fast'!
See that, Masashi'! That's Bunta': son.
You're kidding me!
It sure looked like Bunta was driving it.
The sound alone shows how great he is.
He was flooring the pedal for along time.
No normal 18-year-old has skills like that.
Like father, like son.
But...
...that kind of driving
sure is rough on the engine.
These are tough turns.
But! don't think! lost any time.
No matter the car...
many driver would lose speed on these turns.
I should be safe with this much of a lead.
What?!
What happened? This can't be!
This is humiliating.
I can't shake him off,
even with my technique and power!
What is this?!
Punk...
Don't insult me!
It's almost time.
Iwonder who's ahead,
the Ian-Evo or the Eight-Six'!
Keisuke, you said earlier
that the Ian-Evo would lose if he was in front.
I know from my own experience
that he won't let you run away with the lead.
He sticks right with you like super glue.
If you get irritated and rely on the car's power
to shake him off, the tires deflate.
Damn, he': right on me.
The key is how you use the tires.
Anyone whojumps ahead
without knowing that...
...will lose.
The from tires are losing pressure.
This is irritating. I just can'! stay focused.
Don'! panic. No need to shake him off.
H! win if! keep my lead.
Pm certainly in a more favorable position.
No matter how fast he can tum,
he can't pass me at a comer.
And Pm way faster on the straightaways!
I wasn't wrong.
Taking the lead back there was the right move.
Pm the winner, Kyoichi!
Whenever I turned around
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
The warm wind
Comes back quietly and tenderly
And as I gaze at the sky alone
You smile down upon me
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory
The end is near. What did Takumi
decide during this tough race?
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"Hollow Victory."
Don'! miss it!