"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it': an era
where it travels in a second
Bu! you don'! know what
choice you should take
"Money can'! buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don'! realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can'! even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get moved!
Let': move into the brand new world
Let': dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let': warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That': our law!
No cars ahead!
Make 'W. flashy, Make!
--Yeah!
--Go!
He couldn't have!
We already knew how great he was.
But since this is my last race...
...we can't quit without giving it our best!
What are you, scared?!
You're useless!
You're nothing but dead weight.
--Dead weight?!
--You're ballast,
messing up the power-to-weight ratio!
She gets tough behind the wheel!
I'm not ballast!
I'm not fat! I have a nice body!
Forty-nine kilograms of extra weight!
I weigh 47!
Fine, I've got my pride, too!
Ready, Make'!
We'll put our lives on the line!
Welcome back!
All right. Enter the next turn so
you almost scrape the inside wall!
Got it!
"Act 19: Super Drift"
"Goodnight, Papa.
--'Night.
Natsuki'!
When will I see you again'!
I'm not sure. School starts soon...
Natsuki...
The next turn looks sandy.
--Hug the inside!
--Got it!
No cars ahead! Drift through it!
I couldn't be my usual self
because I was too conscious of him.
Deep down, I believed that no racer
could follow us, no matter how great he was.
But now! see.
I can't race well if my attention
is on what's behind me.
H! never look back again.
Drift here!
There can't be many turns left.
Yeah.
I wonder if he's still chasing her'!
To be honest, I thought the
race would end a lot sooner.
No way!
Even if he can't pass her this time,
he'll win the next race.
He can't pass her.
I'm amazed he's still in the race.
He just had to be the cat on this new course.
Wow, it started!
My name is Make Sate.
Call me!
Sorry about that...
To make this summer memorable,
I would like to race
Akina': Eight-Six at Usui Pass.
That's my wish.
In return for my wish...
...I'll give you my virginity.
Iketani!
What'!
You were spacing out.
It's so obvious that you
were thinking about Mako.
It's not like that!
No need to hide it.
I have to admit that she's a cool girl.
Kenh...
I don't know the details,
but after this race,
you should give it another try.
You'd be a fool to let her go so easily.
I don't care.
Drift here!
There's a car ahead,
but it's still three turns away,
so enter this turn at full speed!
Okay, Sayuki.
Get ready for the car.
It sounds like a race.
Really? I wanna see!
Their downhill technique will
show you how good they are.
Amazing...
lcalled it!
Sayuki can time oncoming traffic perfectly.
She can spot the distant headlights
flashing through the leaves.
"Grip" and stay inside!
Good job, Make. You're right on.
Drift right through here!
No cars ahead! Drift again!
Amazing. Maybe too amazing...
Good racers always leave room for error.
It may look like they're exceeding their limits,
but they only use full
"wheel grip" when exiting a tum.
They ease up on the "wheel grip"
when braking into a tum,
because one mistake on an
unforgiving course means a crash.
But...
...she has no margin for error right now.
She is too focused to even realize it.
Should I mention it to her...
...or not?
It': my job to let her know.
However...
...I don'! want to say anything
to mess up her perfect run.
I've decided.
We're the best team.
How can I not believe in her?
This is her best race ever.
Man, what a charge!
She picked up the pace again.
Any faster, and H! exceed my limit.
Even now, Pm barely in control,
abusing all four tires...
Darn, I may not make it...
This is our last chance to shake him off.
I know.
No cars ahead! Go for it!
He': not following...
Why not?
Mako, you're going in too sharp!
We can't recover! Spin away from him!
Oh, man!
Please don'! hit us!
--We're saved.
--Brilliant.
We lost.
He's so skilled...
...that I almost hate him.
How do you feel'!
We lost...
...but I feel very satisfied.
It reminded me of the excitement
I felt when I first started racing.
We would practice until sunrise.
That same pure sensation...
You went too far at the end,
but you were great until then.
The best race ever.
Sayuki...
Whatever you decide to do from now on,
just know that you have my blessing.
Thanks, Sayuki.
No need (or tears, Make.
Let's just enjoy this glorious moment.
They're back!
I wonder how the race went'!
You think they're going again'!
Probably...
Takumi!
Takumi...
I find it hard to believe, but...
I guess we won't need the second race, huh'!
No second race. It's all over.
I knew it.
Even for Takumi...
No... I didn't want to see him lose like this.
We lost.
Come again'!
What did you just say'!
I said we lost.
Don't make me repeat it.
He's the winner.
What?!
“Yaw
“wow!
I never imagined we could
lose on our own turf.
All I did was follow you,
and I barely did that,
so I don't think I really won the race.
Don't be so modest.
With your skills, you have
the right to rub it in.
But...
We've put in hours of practice here,
so we were very confident.
You chose to chase us,
and we couldn't shake you off.
We accept our defeat, right, Mako'!
Yeah.
Make...
That was by far the best race ever.
Thanks.
You're blushing big time.
You're a mystery.
Your racing ability is extraordinary,
but otherwise you barely seem ordinary.
This is how he usually is.
When he's not racing,
we can't tell if he's awake or asleep.
Hey, thanks a lot.
Itsuki': right, though.
Anyhow, I'm amazed how
young and good you really are.
You should give it another try.
You'd be a fool to let her go so easily.
lketani.
Thank you for tonight...
Mako, I...
Don't be depressed, lketani!
Racers don't need girls, right'!
Right...
Actually, he has a really adorable face.
Hey, what's your name, anyway?
--Takumi Fujiwara...
--ltsuki Takeuchi, 18!
I'm an Aries and type O,
and my favorite car is...
I don't think I asked you...
Anyway, since we're friends now,
how about going swimming
together sometime?
That sounds great!
Kenji?
--Sure.
--How about you, Takumi'!
--Yeah...
--You, too, lketani'!
Yay! Thank you, Sayuki!
Let's go wild and crazy with my Eight-Five!
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let': enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
wand miraculous flower
If men weren't honest with themselves,
mankind would've been extinct long ago.
You're right, boss!
The beginning of a relationship is important.
Make sure that you don't...
Hi, Honey. Pm on my way...
Leaving, boss? Make sure you don'! what?
Next on initial D: "The End of Summer."
Make sure you don'! miss it!