"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Kikanaku natteta
ano CD wo mam sagasou
ltsushika nervous-gachi no futari no tame ni
Speed tozashita kako ga
mezamete iku melody
Chikyuu ga furueru hodo ni
kakushinhan no neraiuchi
Blazin' beat
Hui hodo tsuyoi ai wo abisete
Sakebu kaze hibiku oto de daite
Naked mind, desire
Motomeru koto ni tsumi wa naku
Utagau koto sum wasurete mi wo makasete
Blazin' beat! Yo! Binbin de ikou,
moral wa hashotte ii darou
Shoudo no mama ni tobidasou
Weekend da yo zenin shugo!
M.O.V.E., move, buchigiri hajikeru
Torihada mon no wakuwaku
wo sagasou, it's the time!
"Act 8: Dangerous Car"
His counterattack worked flawlessly!
It was so easy I'm at a loss.
That Ian-Evo is monstrous.
Its extra boost and traction...
No FR can imitate that,
no matter how powerful it is.
You're so right.
There's no denying the mechanical
superiority of a 4WD car.
This just became a tough race for Ryosuke.
Will he have an opportunity to regain the lead'!
I doubt it.
RYOsukQQ!
You carry the pride and
hope of all Gunma': racers.
Don'! you dare lose!
My complex about passes has vanished.
I just don'! buy the idea of "charisma."
Analyzing this superstitious illusion
in the cold light of day,
I've realized that it': actually nothing
but experience and refined technique.
Now that I know that, Pm not afraid of Ryosuke.
Why? Because Pm superior
to him in that category.
Hey,Takumi'!
What do you think happened in Akagi'!
Maybe it's over.
Who do you think won'!
I have no idea.
I can't tell, because I lost to that Ian-Evo
before I saw his full capabilities.
I'm getting upsetjust talking to you about it.
--Sorry.
--Don't be sorry.
I mean, talking to you is helping me get it out.
I was so depressed all day today.
After the engine blew up,
the Len-Eve's driver told me
that he didn't consider it a race.
He said we would race for real
when I had a better car.
He did?
The way he said it,
it sounded like he was reasoning
with me like a schoolteacher
instead of bragging about his victory.
My pride just won't let me forget what he said.
"Suzuki Motors"
My pridejust won't let me forget what he said.
Well...
...let's get started.
By tomorrow night,
there will be a rumor in Akina
that the "Fujiwara Tofu"
car has been resurrected.
It': a finely tuned car, Kyoichi.
It has surprisingly fine cornering abilities,
and it can accelerate at any rpm.
It turns easily and exits comers swiftly.
Its acceleration is unbeatable.
What a scary car!
It': overwhelming to observe it up close.
But it': not like I just realized this.
I found it out yesterday.
Wow! Ryosuke bumped the guardrail!
He had to do that to keep up with that Evo Ill.
Look at this time.
Amazing! If the Evo Ill keeps this up,
he'll surpass the course record.
Ryosuke isn't slow.
That Evo Ill is going really fast.
Hello, this is corner #35.
The Evo Ill is still ahead.
Got it.
Keisuke, will he be okay'!
The Len-Eve's maintaining his pace.
He may just run away with the victory.
Don't worry.
My brother will overcome this predicament.
Sudo sure is fast.
Most of us here probably didn't
expect him to be this fast.
I certainly didn't. But my brother did.
Using the data collected
at various checkpoints
during last night's race against the Eight-Six,
he was able to calculate Sudo': abilities
more precisely than I ever could.
Sol believe...
...that my brother will win in the end.
The misfiring system and
the 4WD are a killer combo.
Full acceleration in low gears won'! cut it.
But I may get a chance at a high-speed comer.
I knew it!
He isn't attacking from another angle.
Why not?
His passiveness is eerie.
Has he given up?
No,I know very well that he isn't like that.
He will attack.
I know Pm in the superior position,
but I feel like he': hunting me down.
Have I not yet overcome
my complex about Ryosuke?
A victory over him will erase that.
Pm ready for you, Ryosuke.
All my tires still have full traction.
What a thrilling race this is!
I only have one chance.
I need to attack precisely...
...into the flickering loophole.
Ryosuke is right on him.
But the Evo Ill is going fast.
He isn't slowing his pace at all!
It doesn't look good for Ryosuke Takahashi.
The finish line is right after this corner.
His defeat has become more certain now.
There!
The Evo Ill is still ahead!
This right tum is my chance!
Kyoichi, your weakness lies
in your unconquered fear of turning right.
Frankly...
...you stink at turning right!
What?!
--The FC took the outside!
--Amazing!
The Evo Ill is completely blocked by the FC!
Dam! I can'! utilize the 4WD': traction
or the misfiring system in this situation!
Incredible! The FC is cornering
while blocking the Evo Ill!
Go, Ryosuke Takahashi!
Go! Go! Go!
--Go, Ryosuke!
--He's going!
--He's ahead!
--They switched!
That's it, Ryosuke!
Keep it up! Keep going!
He did it!
A course record! A super win!
Eat our dust!
The Red Suns save Gunma!
--Yeah!
--He did it!
I can't believe Kyoichi couldn't beat him.
An amazing course record.
I've never seen Ryosuke go that fast.
Why is he faster in battles than usual'!
My brother usually leaves
enough of a safety margin
to avoid crashing during our time trials.
When he's forced to raise the bar,
a record like this is the natural result.
That Evo Ill was a tough opponent.
So he got a bit serious.
Wow,
What a win!
That corner was amazing!
I want to ask you something, Ryosuke.
What's the difference between us'!
Why can't I beat you'!
I just don't get it.
Please tell me.
In my opinion, your technique
is almost as good as mine.
No need for consolation. Just tell me why!
I'm saying that it's not
because of your technique.
Your weakness is your right turn.
Not all right turns...
...but at certain right turns,
your weakness surfaces.
Right turns'!
To the right of the center line is a "dead zone"
occupied by opposing traffic.
You can't attack a right-hand corner
without worrying about a head-on collision.
No one can give it 100%.
But with experience and effort,
you can come close to 100%.
Do you understand, Kyoichi'!
That's the difference.
In motorsports, you don't have
to worry about opposing traffic.
The Gymkhana circuit
doesn't have two-way traffic.
And your home course,
Nikko lrohazaka, is one-way,
so there's no opposing traffic.
In your counterattack,
you always stay outside at right-hand corners.
I read that as meaning
you're afraid of the inside.
In the race against the Eight-Six,
you showed me too much,
which is why you lost.
You beat me, Ryosuke.
My belief that I had caught up
with you was an illusion.
You have street "charisma."
It was amazing!
I realized again how great
Ryosuke Takahashi really is.
Anyway, the Ian-Evo squad
"storm" that threatened Gunma
has blown itself out,
and peace has been restored.
Yeah. I should've gone to watch the race.
By the way, were Takumi and ltsuki with you'!
I didn't see them there.
Maybe Takumi didn't feel like it
after his loss the other night.
I'm sure he didn't.
Even we are still in shock.
He specifically told me
he wouldn't go to Akagi.
I wonder what changed his mind.
I'm so happy that Ryosuke Takahashi won!
Now it's official that
Gunma': standard is very high.
I'll see you in class!
Hey! You won't believe this,
Takumi.The other day...
Wait,Takumi!
I'm sorry, but I don't feel like talking to you.
"A few days later"
What'! My dad's Eight-Six'!
It must be a mistake.
I don't know anything about it.
One of our team members says
he saw it in Akina one night.
It was a three-door "panda" Trueno.
I don't think it was ours.
Where is your dad's car, anyway?
I don't really know.
We towed it from Akagi,
and my dad took it somewhere after that.
What about your morning deliveries?
I'm using a pickup truck my dad brought in.
Don't tell me that your legendary Eight-Six
is at a scrap yard right now.
I'll cry!
I doubt it.
My dad said he would put in another engine.
Seriously? What kind of engine?
I doubt it'll be another normal 4AG engine.
Maybe it'll be a turbo!
I have no interest in that, really.
Why is that'!
I think that, of all parts,
the engine is the most
important element of a car.
--| guess so.
--It's like the brain in a human body.
Hey, Takumi...
People usually compare it to the human heart.
Is that right'!
It's the heart, then.
I'd just hate to have another engine in it.
It would feel like a different car.
I guess I can see that.
You're attached to it.
I can understand how you feel...
...but we can't help wondering
what kind of engine it'll have.
How does it feel, Bunta'!
It's getting better,
but since the engine is so good,
the suspension can't catch up.
The engine is that good, huh'!
Yeah, I love it.
It sounds very tempting.
I may want to ride with you next time.
This car is very scary.
That's not for you to say, Bunta.
I already know how scary your driving can be.
Let me give you a glimpse.
What'!
Hey, Bunta!
How did that happen?!
You know, I needed to use this
as a wall to hold up my whole body.
I used to think the side G-force in pass racing
wasn't worthy of a bucket seat.
But I think my bones will bruise
if we don't put one in now.
I've had enough for today.
This is one tough customer.
But that makes it more exciting.
I still haven't decided
how I'm going to set it up.
I'll take my time and enjoy it.
I need to consider that inept Takumi
is going to be driving it, too.
Inept, he says.
Takumi'! Is he kidding?
It's kind of boring being in high school.
You think so'!
I can't wait to start working.
Until you have a real job, you're still a child.
I wanna work and make money.
With a good job, I can have my own car.
I can't buy anything now. How pathetic!
Don't be so impatient.
Whether we like it or not,
we're graduating next spring.
I can't wait...
...because there's nothing
worthwhile at school.
You seem down, Takumi.
Wait!
Why have you been avoiding me'!
Did I do something wrong,
or say something hurtful?
If so, please tell me. I'll apologize!
Not really.
--Then what's wrong'!
--Nothing's wrong.
Something is clearly wrong!
We were okay until recently.
Now you seem distant. It's not fair.
What's wrong, Takumi'!
I don't know why you're so worked up
about someone like me.
It doesn't matter.
It's not like we're dating.
That doesn't make any sense.
What's going on'!
Don't follow me.
Good luck with the Mercedes guy.
Leave me alone.
What...?
How did hem?
Furikaereba itsudatte
Kawaranu kimi no egao ga aim
Arukitsukare tachidomaru hi mo
Chiisa nu yorokobi no hi mo
Kono ryoute ni kakaekirenai
Al' wo oshiete kureta
Atatakaku
Sotto yasashiku yomigaeru kaze wa
{ma hitori sora wo
Mitsumeteru boku ni hohoendeiru
Mada ano hi no mama no
Mabushisa de te wo futteiru
Kimi wa everlasting memory
The Eight-Six is finally back!
How powerful is it?
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"The New Eight-Six."
Don'! miss it!