"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it': an era
where it travels in a second
Bu! you don'! know what
choice you should take
"Money can'! buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don'! realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can'! even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get moved!
Let': move into the brand new world
Let': dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let': warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That': our law!
I mean, look at this Eight-Six
with its ugly wheels.
It's embarrassing!
I'm crying!
I never thought anyone would be
driving an Eight-Five in this day and age!
It suits you well, though, kid!
Don't let any scooters tailgate you!
That's it! They're gonna pay!
Here we go!
Takumi! Ohh! Ohhh!
P... Please...
Take good care of my Eight-Five!
"Act 11: Shingo Arrives!"
It's not worth it, Takumi!
Ta... Takumi...
Slow down, Takumi!
You nailed it!
What the heck'!
Hey, that car's right on our tail!
It must be some Akina punk.
You picked the wrong cars to tailgate!
I see...
Wanna play with us'!
That's enough, Takumi!
Stop the car!
"Curve ahead"
I said stop!
TakumiH
Unbelievable...
Is this really my Eight-Five'!
He is not bad at all...
No way!
Isn't that the Eight-Five'!
The one we saw at the pass'!
There's no way an Eight-Five
could keep up with us!
You're right! It's that Eight-Five!
Those punks lied to us!
It must be...
...an Eight-Six!
Here it is!
What?
It won'! accelerate down the hill at all...
And these wheels won'! grip the road at all...
Darn, he is so fast!
This is so slow.
I guess it': time for that move.
You won't pass me, no matter what!
What?!
What just happened?!
How did he pass me'!
That's not an Eight-Five.
That's an Eight-Six!
A well-tuned Eight-Six...
What a big roll!
Was it...
...an Eight-Five'!
He went right through us.
That Eight-Five was spooky!
Was it...
...a ghost?!
- Want a coffee?
- Yeah.
--Here.
--Thank you.
Iketani told me... that your
downhill skills were abnormal.
Abnormal?
I don't think so...
You just can't see it yourself.
I never imagined that a car could run like that.
You've changed my perception.
It was that shocking.
I'm sorry it was so scary for you.
No need for an apology, Takumi.
I've never been this happy before!
Huh?
I realized that it wasn't all
about the car's capabilities.
If you have skills, you can even
maneuver an Eight-Five like that.
I fell in love with my car!
I'll take good care of it.
I'll train hard, starting tomorrow.
I don't care if people laugh at me.
My Eight-Five is the best!
Hey, let's go for a drive with
a couple of girls next time!
--Sure...
--No blowing me off this time, okay'!
--| mean it,Takumi!
--| promise.
The ocean, the girls, the bikinis...here I come!
All right!!
M31513!
You came back to me... as handsome as ever.
I'm going to cry...
--Are you trying to run over me, ltsuki?
--All right!!
We'll start training today!
We'll practice drifting with lower-grade tires.
Count me in, too!
Check out this cool sticker!
What...'!!
It's all right, isn't it'!
Yeah, sure, not bad...
Now I'm officially a member
of Team Speed Stars!
--The sticker looks crooked.
--Ta ke it off...
I should practice before I forget Takumi':
downhill techniques from last night.
What?! He let you in his Eight-Six'!
He sure did...
...though it wasn't the Eight-Six.
What's with the meaningful laugh'!
"Confess, ltsuki!
--Should I tell you'!
--Wanna drink gasoline?
--Okay, I'll tell you!
Well, he drove my Eight-Five
at the Akina downhill last night.
It was beyond my imagination!
I've never seen anything like it!
Even way before a corner,
we were drifting sideways.
All I could see was the blur
of scenery in the windshield.
It was miraculous!
He drifted with your Eight-Five'!
It doesn't even have LSD!
It was so quick.
We passed twojerks back to back
at the downhill hairpin turns.
I've never felt so alive!
Do you believe him, boss'!
I knowTakumi is good, but with an Eight-Five'!
It's hard to believe that any driver
could do that in an Eight-Five.
I know it's hard to believe,
but I saw what I saw.
If ltsuki is telling the truth,
that means that Takumi': adaptability
is far beyond what I imagined.
Since they both have the same body,
maybe they have similar maneuverability?
I doubt that.
That Eight-Five is a joke,
compared to the Eight-Six Bunta has built
and modified over the years.
A joke?!
You mean,Takumi can
drive pretty much any car'!
Just as long as they have the FR layout,
he can bring out their full potential.
Not just anyone can drive an Eight-Six.
You have to have mastered
the basic skills to drive one.
Bunta used to say...
"An Eight-Six trains the driver."
That car... had a Night Kids sticker on it.
It had street racing written all over it.
You can totally tell modified cars from others
by looking at how they run.
Yeah.
Lately, those Night Kids come to Akina a lot.
What do they want'!
Well, since their leader Nakazato lost,
I don't think anyone from their team
will come out for a rematch.
I almost feel bad for him.
Now that Takeshi has lost to that Eight-Six,
he can't act all invincible anymore.
May I help you?
--Two coffees.
--Sure.
I heard that the Eight-Six driver
in the Speed Stars is just a kid.
I don't know how good this kid is...
...but when I beat that Eight-Six,
I'll be better than Takeshi.
I'll be the fastest one in Night Kids.
I don't know, Shingo.
I know you're fast downhill,
but I've heard this kid is abnormal.
I know I can take him fair and square,
but I have a more interesting idea,
which will ensure my victory.
Wham?!
You'll see. I'll show him an
impressively dangerous downhill.
The world only needs one downhill specialist.
The Eight-Six is outdated.
I'll make sure to send it to a scrap yard.
Wha...
Shingo Shah of Night Kids...
...is the fastest downhill racer in Gunma.
Where is Ryosuke'!
My brother is locked in his room,
staring at his computer screen.
He sure likes doing that.
He's the only street racer in Gunma
who trains by staring at a computer screen.
I wonder what would happen if my brother
and the Eight-Six of Mount Akina raced?
There is no way Ryosuke would lose to him.
Ryosuke knows all about that Eight-Six now.
I'm sure he has all the data he needs
to create a simulation of
a winning race in his head.
No street racer knows more
about cars than my brother.
I can't imagine him losing,
considering his exceptional skills.
Well,then...
But that Eight-Six won't lose, either.
That high-speed drifting...
...and his delicate brake control.
He's exceptional, too.
As a fellow FR driver,
I may have fallen for the
way that Eight-Six runs.
Keisuke...
if they race, one will lose.
I don't want my brother to lose,
but I don't want to see
that Eight-Six lose, either.
Strange, isn't it'!
Oh, sorry!
--Did you get wet'!
--No.
--Hold on...
--Sure.
Why don't we go somewhere together again'!
We can go to the mountains,
or the highlands, or the ocean.
--We're on summer vacation!
--Yeah...
Let's make a lot of memories!
We should.
Takumi, I wouldn't mind going with you...
...on an overnight trip.
When is your next day off'! This Sunday?
It depends, really...
Do you want to take me for a drive again then'!
--With that car'!
--Yeah.
No blowing me off this time, Takumi!
Do you mind if ltsukijoins us'!
The three of us'!
I was hoping...
...you could find someone for him.
Yeah...
He's a good guy, but he's shy.
I didn't know you were so thoughtful.
I just thought it would be good for him...
Thank you very much!
Sure, I'll ask around.
Thanks.
I'm sure I'll find someone perfect for ltsuki.
That was awesome!
Maybe I should try it, too.
I'm getting the hang of
moving the rear sideways.
It's all about the timing.
You pull the emergency brake to start the drift.
But, lketani...
I didn't see Takumi pull the emergency brake
even once the other night.
Takumi uses the foot pedal brake
to shift the weight.
Don't worry, you're along way from that!
Yeah...
We usually go into a
corner and then accelerate
to skid the rear tires right before coming out,
but that's an elementary
technique called Power Slide
and is not a true drift.
"Keiichi Tsuchiya's Drift Lesson" Takumi drifts
into a corner and controls the skid at the end
"Keiichi Tsuchiya': Drift Lesson"
to stabilize the car-- a true drift.
To stabilize the car-- a true drift.
That's the fastest way to turn,
and it looks good, too.
I see.You've done some research.
I was bored while my S13 was in the shop,
so I read some books.
I wanna try the sidespin, too.
I'm so excited!
I think I'm ready for the next step.
Instead of a straight line,
I'll try it in a low-speed turn.
Good luck, lketani!
Watch out for other cars!
We'll be there later!
It': really hard to be in
total control of your car.
I wish I could be like Takumi.
I wanna ride with him one more time.
Watching him drive my car
is the best way to learn.
What'!
I wasn't paying attention...
Darn!
You hit my bumper!
Now I really can't let you go!
Pass me if you can!
"Mt. Akina Skate Center"
Speed Stars?!
That was close...
A little tap on the bumper right before a turn...
That's all you need to destabilize a pathetic FR.
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
$0 HO one IHTQFVQHQS
Never stop, I don't want to stop
Even if you cry because of a sacrificed love
Aim for the peak, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! The warning chime is so cheap!
The sheep should clear the road
'Cuz Pm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy motivation is total stimulation
You tried to escape,
but anywhere is a safety zone
Something is within your grasp
and something is forgotten
Even if the world ends it will never change
Beasty shout, no one can touch you
Cross over now to the time of an intense dream
Rage your dream, split the darkness
Like a streak to the peak
Erase the freezing darkness worldwide
Rage your dream, and open the road
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
A point 01 second knockdown
Reverberations left behind,
disappear to the next town
The losers are left in the dust
Let': ignore the constraints of logic
'Cause theyWe a pain
A streaker runs naked across the street
Something they would know
Rage your dream,
continue on the unending road
Don'! look back on your love or your past
Go forward and you'll shine brightly
Rage your dream, you're living in the now
"What do I want right now?
"Yeah.
To spend more time with Takumi.
To go on dates more often,
and make a lot of memories as a couple.
We're on summer vacation,
but Takumi is too busy working.
And even when we are together,
he's always staring off into the distance...
--...and isn't really there for me...
--We don't have much time, so...
Next on Initial D, "The FR Killer."
Don'! miss it.