"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawarujidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can'! buy my love name
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doom' n1' tada dakiai
Al' ga nai koto n1' k1' ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru ma: ni sakebou ze hol!
In the midnight dream
lki sue tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sue safety homo ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get moved!
Let': move into the brand new world
Let': dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mam aikyou
Kimeru toko duke no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji duke wa tooshi ikiteru
That': our law!
"Act 18: Hot Winds 8' Furious Driving!"
She': fast!
Pm in trouble. Can I keep up?
If she can, so can l.
Come on!
Stay way inside on the next curve!
That's the way, Mako!
An obstacle! Move inside.
Not bad.
He's not like other racers. He's still with us.
Good. There's more to look forward to.
I wonder how long he can keep it up'!
We're just getting started.
Man,I'm not racing.
Pm just "riding" the race,
like a roller coaster.
Pm so out of sync that it': scary.
But if I fall behind, I won'! be able to catch up.
Stay close!
I never realized that course
knowledge was so important.
Losing my focus would mean
crashing into a wall or falling off a cliff.
No wonder people are talking
about that Eight-Six lately.
We can't shake him off easily.
He is about to experience the
terror of Usui': severe turns.
--Narrow right turn ahead!
--Okay!
She': fast! Damn!
But I gotta stay close!
If she can, I can!
Takumi said that if she could make
it around the corners, so could he.
That's exactly what he said.
That's an unbelievably childish idea.
What's wrong with his head'!
But it's amazing that he said that.
Someone with lesser abilities
wouldn't think that.
He can probably control his run
if he doesn't go beyond his limitations.
Of course he can!
But he's racing against Mako,
who knows everything there is
to know about this course.
I'm sure she enters each
corner as fast as possible
so Takumi will have to do the same,
even though he knows
nothing about this course.
I get chills just thinking about it.
Yeah, it demands both
technique and true courage.
One mistake...
...and he's finished.
He': racing a Sileighty...
What the heck is that?
He's right behind me!
Why'! Am I not going fast enough?
No,you're doing great, Make.
But he's on me!
Don't worry about him,
or you'll mess up your rhythm.
Leave what's going on behind us to me.
It's only just started.
Let's enjoy this awesome race!
Right. I trust you.
Just believe in your partner!
You and I are the fastest team in Usui!
If the mouse gets away, it's over.
If not, we keep switching
positions until someone wins.
It's a "sudden-death death match."
With this rule, you should go in front first.
It won't end with one race,
but at least you get one practice.
It's better to lose in the second race.
I'll chase her first.
Think it over,Takumi!
This is my race, so let me decide.
Pm in trouble.
I chose to chase her 'cuzl didn't
want her chasing me, but...
...this is tough.
"Takahashi"
“Takahashi” I! is very crucial to
determine the correct entering speed
"The Theory of the Fastest on the Street" It is very
crucial to determine the correct entering speed
"The Theory of the Fastest on the Street"
for the corners on any unfamiliar course.
Keisuke': loss and Nakazato
losing his lead were due to this.
Course knowledge gives
the racer an advantage,
regardless of his technique.
So, how can I beat the Eight-Six?
According to my theory,
I can win even at Akina Pass.
Man, I was too optimistic.
Hook a risky challenge.
The difference of a few
inches and a little speed
at the start of a tum makes
a huge difference at the exit.
Too wide!
I hit the guardrail!
Darn, I gotta stay close!
Each heart-pounding moment
helps a racer grow bigger and better.
With his exceptional concentration
and sense, his refined technique...
wand, of course, my Eight-Six,
which I have perfected over the years...
...he won'! lose.
"Nagano Prefecture"
"Karuizawa-machi"
I wonder what happened?
Maybe it's over.
It's not over until they come back.
This race is one-sided,
no matter how you look at it.
But, lketani...
He's never had a race
that's been favorable for him.
Nakazato': R32 was monstrous.
And the duct tape death match
was Takumi': first try.
But Takumi always had one friend...
Akina Pass.
The pass that he drove every day for years.
Does the location make that
much difference, though?
If he had driven here a few times,
it might have been different,
but this is his very first time here.
Well, but...
By the way, lketani...
What the heck was that girl
doing sitting next to Mako'!
How should I know'!
I noticed that, too.
This is a race, but she
went in as if it was normal.
I don't know the details.
All I know is that they're best friends,
and from the beginning,
they were always analyzing
and developing their technique together.
Isn't she like a rally navigator?
--That makes it worse for Takumi.
--Yeah.
No way! He won't lose!
But with a good navigator,
Mako can concentrate fully on driving.
Obstacle ahead!
--Avoid it and cut inside!
--Yeah.
He keeps up with our fast pace...
was if Make': best isn'! fast enough.
He': good!
Mako, C-121 is coming up.
We'll shake him off there!
We'll drift from the very beginning.
Let's show him what we're made of
at Usui': most difficult turn.
Got it.That's right!
I'll show him how drifting should be done!
No one else has ever
cleared the turn at full speed.
Are Make and Sayuki here tonight'!?
I haven't seen them yet.
I wanna see the Sileighty': drift.
Here at C-121 is the best place for it.
'Cuz it's really hard.
It's the hardest.
You're considered an advanced racer here
if you can drift through this turn.
Advanced in Usui means the best anywhere.
--Yeah. --If you don't have
the courage to come in fast,
you won't have enough
speed to drift to the end.
All the first-timers mess it up.
But some can actually do it, right'!
A few.
But only Mako': Sileighty
does it at full speed.
I don't know how fast she goes,
but no one else has managed it yet.
Someone is coming down.
Hear that squealing? They're coming in fast!
There!
--The Sileighty!
--It's Mako and Sayuki!
Who's following them'!
Are they racing?!
An Eight-Six?!
No cars ahead!
Make 'W. flashy, Make!
--Yeah!
--Go!
They're in the turn!
That fool came into the turn
at the same speed as Mako!
Doesn't he know how difficult C-121 is?!
Courage alone won't let him clear the corner!
He has guts, following Make into this comer.
But at this speed, there': no turning back.
C-121's exit narrows severely.
There is only one ideal line to the exit,
though there seem to be others.
Can you find it, your first time on this course?
He couldn't have!
--He cleared it.
--Unbelievable.
Who's that Eight-Six'!
Could he be... the famous
Eight-Six of Mount Akina'!
I have goose bumps!
Whatjust happened?
Four-wheel drift at full speed
is ranked as "Ultra D" difficulty.
Even Make missed the
ideal line by three inches.
But he was right on it.
We can'! win. We chose a
monster as our opponent.
No! You can't swing that much here!
You couldn't have told me that sooner?
What's wrong'! Focus! This isn't like you!
Can't you tell, Mako'!
That Eight-Six is unreal.
He's way out of our league.
What happened to your usual stubbornness?
It's not even over and you're giving up'!
Not me!
I guess I am...
Fine! I didn't know you were a quitter.
I'll do it myself!
We already knew how great he was.
But since this is my last race...
...we can't quit without giving it our best!
What are you, scared?!
You're useless!
You're nothing but dead weight.
--Dead weight?!
--You're freight,
messing up the power-to-weight ratio!
She gets tough behind the wheel!
I'm not freight!
I'm not fat! I have a nice body!
Forty-nine kilograms of extra weight!
I weigh 47!
Fine, I've got my pride, too!
Ready, Make'!
We'll put our lives on the line!
Welcome back!
All right. Enter the next turn so
you almost scrape the inside wall!
Got it!
Not bad.
I improved while recklessly chasing her.
I can feel the rhythm now!
Pm synched in!
Not many comers left now...
I'll just have to attack
each comer as well as I can!
I want no regrets.
My pride as Usui's fastest is on the line.
Ai ni tsukare hate samayotteta koro
Yokubou duke ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure nu unmeiwa
Mujaki nu hitomi ni miserarete yuku
Sake bum no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku kimi o daite
Talia hitotsu kono omoi o shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi o kanadeyou...
Kagayaku mirai e
Kazoe kirenai hodo tashikame aou
Jounetsu yo eien e todoke
Sake bum no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani o ushinattemo
kono ude o hanasanai
Utsukushiku karen ni sake...
Kiseki no hana yo
Buma, do you thinkTakumi has
a chance against the Sileighty?
--Who knows?
--Who knows?!
I sell tofu, not predictions.
--I'll have Gunmo and Atsuage.
--I have seasoned that Eight-Six.
No one can touch it downhill.
It': up to the driver.
We'll see next week.
What if! bought Momen and KinugoshLtoo?
Next on initial D: "Super Drift."
--It's a must-see.
"Don't miss it!