"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it': an era
where it travels in a second
Bu! you don'! know what
choice you should take
"Money can'! buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don'! realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can'! even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get moved!
Let': move into the brand new world
Let': dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let': warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That': our law!
That punk!
Hey, you!
I know you're the one who
hit me from behind yesterday.
Are you kidding me'!
--That was your fault.
"What?
Your car was going so slow
that I couldn't anticipate it.
I never thought you could
attack a corner that slowly.
I tried to brake, but... bump.
What did you say?!
Calm down, lketani!
If you insist, then we'll race under my rules.
If I lose, I'll be on the ground
begging for your forgiveness.
What do you mean, "your" rules'!
It's nothing.
We call it the "duct tape death match."
Duct tape death match'!
I hear the Speed Stars' Eight-Six
is a downhill specialist.
Tell this Eight-Six kid
that I'll be waiting here
next Saturday at 10 p.m.
I'll see you then.
I think that punkjust challenged you,Takumi.
He didn't recognize your face, though.
Go for it,Takumi!
Duct tape or whatever...
Beat that jerk badly and
make him beg for forgiveness!
It sounds too risky, ltsuki.
He can't steer in this race.
But, lketani...
Takumi beat the FD and the R32.
His little rule won't make any difference.
I'm sure he's been practicing a lot this way.
Takumi, it's too risky.
Don't take the bait.
I have no desire to, really...
Good for you. Just ignore him.
"Act 13: First Date"
What'! A duct tape death match'!
--Yeah.
"That's reckless.
Is Takumi...'!
As usual, he's calm and unexcited.
He's not into it at all.
I want him to do it!
It would be so refreshing to beat that jerk
and make him apologize!
He drives a Civic, the rival
of the Levin and the Trueno.
In my day, we raced in a variety
of ways under different rules,
but the duct tape death match was
one of the most dangerous ones.
Is it really that dangerous?
It doesn't sound like it.
Itsuki, get in your car and try it for yourself,
then you'll understand.
--Well...
--Okay.
Don't let go of your right hand,
and steer all the way to either side.
Sure.
This is as far as it goes!
Leave the wheel there and come out.
Okay.
See how much you steered.
Sure.
What?! This is it?!
I steered as far as I could.
See;
How can you turn corners like this'!
Let alone drive the pass...
Steering can only be used to initiate the turn.
You have to turn by sliding the rear tires.
--All the corners.
--What?!
But Takumi is a drift expert, so he can manage.
It's not that easy.
You can't counter,
which makes it harder to control the drift.
Oversteering means a spin,
but if you go "under" into
a turn, that'll be the end.
This rule definitely favors an FF driver.
--He drives an EG6, right'!
--Yes.
Its accelerator eliminates oversteering,
so he can attack corners at full speed.
Its side brake also eliminates "under."
But an FR such as the Eight-Six
needs to continuously drift
through a narrow area as if
walking on a tightrope...
It's better to avoid it.
Darn...
Talk like this may trigger his interest.
Uh, boss'!
--Isn't that Kenji'!
--Oh...
lketani...
I did a little research on
that punk from the other day.
He's Shingo Shah of the Myogi Night Kids.
Shingo Shah of the Night Kids...
He's their number two,
but he's confident enough to call himself
the fastest downhill racer of the Night Kids.
He'll stop at nothing to reach his goals,
so he isn't popular with his teammates,
especially their leader, Nakazato.
I see.That's why he's challenging Takumi.
So that he can take over the Night Kids.
He's been spreading a
rumor about this already.
A rumor'!
A rumor that the Speed Stars are scared
and avoiding Shingo': challenge.
And he mentions nothing about duct tape.
He's making us look bad.
What a jerk!
He's trying to drag Takumi
into the race no matter what.
Oh!
Takumi...
I have no interest in racing him at all, really.
That's good.
You don't have to accept all the
challenges that come your way.
"Forget about it.
--Yeah...
Whatever happened to
the race with the Eight-Six'!
I'm all ready to go.
It's up to him now.
Don't worry...
I'll drag him out, no matter what.
Looks like it'll be an interesting race.
Takeshi!
Shingo, I hear you're
planning something big...
Do what you want,
but don't do anything to insult
the name of the Night Kids.
What's so funny'!
Isn't it you who has insulted our name'!
What'!
I wonder who lost to that obsolete Eight-Six...
...with a powerful R32'!
Shingo...
A loser should be off sulking somewhere.
Still acting like a leader
and giving me a lecture...
You make me laugh.
I'll avenge you, Nakazato.
Be thankful.
Shingo, someday you'll find out...
...how fierce that Eight-Six is.
Well,Takeshi is on the skids.
He's pitiful, really.
Shingo, you're the new
leader of the Night Kids.
First, I have to send the Eight-Six
of Mount Akina to the scrap yard.
Hello! This is Takeuchi...
Is this Saori'!
Itsuki'!
Of course, I remember you.
Yeah. A drive to Akina Lake'!
Okay.
Really?!
I'll meet you at that bus stop at 1:00, then.
Yeah, bye!
Yeah! I just put an end to years of no girlfriend!
I'll make it count!
Here you go.
Hey, Dad...
What is it'!
Is a duct tape death match...'!
No, never mind.
A duct tape death match...
Takumi...
You're good at driving cars.
Takumi, I wouldn't mind going with you...
...on an overnight trip.
Pm very conscious of her lately...
Thank you very much!
Where is ltsuki'!
He was just washing his car...
Where did he go'!
"Practice Guide"
I see, I see...
Is this where you were hiding?
Um, I, uh, was just resting...
It's rare to see you with a book.
That's just, uh...!
Let's see: "Love Manual:
How to Impress Your Date"!
That book is just...
The reason you're reading
this book is because...
...you have a date'!
Yes!
Is it with that Saori girl you mentioned before?
What about me?!
I picked it up at a bookstore yesterday
and have been studying it.
You seem to have very little
advice on things like this.
That hurts, though you're
probably right about that.
Things are easier nowadays.
In my day, we had to feel our way through...
Let me see: "You should
have her by the third date.
Create a romantic setting for your first kiss..."
I got that covered, boss!
So, like I mentioned before,
I would like to take a day off.
That's why... Sure.
I envy you, you little...
Hook cool!
I wonder where she ism?
I'm here, ltsuki!
I'm so happy!
Welcome--
I don't need gas.
I came to get the answer to my invitation.
You did tell him, didn't you'!
Yeah. He said he had no interest in it.
That's a laugh.
I didn't know that the Eight-Six was a chicken.
He can't be scared of a
duct tape death match, can he'!
That's all right. I'll make him want to do it.
So cute!
"Ropeyflay Depot"
We street racers don't talk
about "turning" a corner.
We "attack" it.
Maybe I should get a license.
Why not'! I'll teach you how to drive.
I'll think about it.
Oh, wow, Mount Fuji ofAkina!
It's so beautiful!
Well, girls are suckers for romance...
The first kiss should be at a romantic setting...
The first kiss...
Now is perfect. Go for it, ltsuki!
Wham?!
Itsuki?!
Sorry...
Yeah...
An awkward silence... What should I do?
I found you.
An 5G6? He bumped me.
Am I going too slowly for him?
He': on my tail.
Darn, I can't look bad in front ofSaori!
Saori...
I gotta speed up.
Hang on for a bit!
Stop, ltsuki!
This is a street race!
I can't stop now!
I have to protect Saori...
Listen up, ltsuki got in an accident!
"What?
"Where?
Akina Pass.
They're at the city hospital.
Can you head over there now'!
Sure.
"City Hospital"
Are you okay, ltsuki'!
Iketani,Takumi!
So, what happened?
It's nothing. It's not as bad as it looks, really.
They're keeping me here to
do some tests,just in case.
Weren't you with Saori'!
She only had a few scratches,
so she went home.
I steered my best to
protect the passenger side.
What happened to your Eight-Five'!
I spun it well, so only the
trunk area was damaged.
Okay, you're done.
--Take care.
--Thank you very much.
I was going down the pass
when an EG6 started tailgating me.
An EGG'! Was 'W. him'!
Maybe. It was a red EG6.
He pushed me from behind at a corner...
That punk did it again!
Dam...
I'll do it.
Duct tape or whatever,
I'll accept the challenge!
Takumi, wait up!
Takumi?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't let him drag you into it.
This whole thing is ridiculous!
Don't do it, Takumi!
I won't lose, no matter what.
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
$0 HO one IHTQFVQHQS
Never stop, I don't want to stop
Even if you cry because of a sacrificed love
Aim for the peak, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! The warning chime is so cheap!
The sheep should clear the road
'Cuz Pm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy motivation is total stimulation
You tried to escape,
but anywhere is a safety zone
Something is within your grasp
and something is forgotten
Even if the world ends it will never change
Beasty shout, no one can touch you
Cross over now to the time of an intense dream
Rage your dream, split the darkness
Like a streak to the peak
Erase the freezing darkness worldwide
Rage your dream, and open the road
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
A point 01 second knockdown
Reverberations left behind,
disappear to the next town
The losers are left in the dust
Let': ignore the constraints of logic
'Cause theyWe a pain
A streaker runs naked across the street
Something they would know
Rage your dream,
continue on the unending road
Don'! look back on your love or your past
Go forward and you'll shine brightly
Rage your dream, you're living in the now
Wasn't it wrong to involve Itsuki
and make him spin out like that, Shingo?
It': okay, as long as I can drag out the Eight-Six.
But...
Since I know for sure that I'll
beat him with the duct tape rule,
just winning isn't enough fun.
H! give you a flashy show.
Next on initial D, "Evolving Drift!"
I'll make sure he can taste
the fear of the downhill.
Don'! miss it!