"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Kikanaku natteta
ano CD wo mam sagasou
ltsushika nervous-gachi no futari no tame ni
Speed tozashita kako ga
mezamete iku melody
Chikyuu ga furueru hodo ni
kakushinhan no neraiuchi
Blazin' beat
Hui hodo tsuyoi ai wo abisete
Sakebu kaze hibiku oto de daite
Naked mind, desire
Motomeru koto ni tsumi wa naku
Utagau koto sum wasurete mi wo makasete
Blazin' beat! Yo! Binbin de ikou,
moral wa hashotte ii darou
Shoudo no mama ni tobidasou
Weekend da yo zenin shugo!
M.O.V.E., move, buchigiri hajikeru
Torihada mon no wakuwaku
wo sagasou, it's the time!
"Act 4: Hollow Victory"
It's always like this when Takumi races.
The tension in the air is the same.
I always give up on him,
but he always wins.
lketani and Kenji keep saying
that Takumi has no chance against the Ian-Evo.
I wonder if they're right.
He has defeated all the opponents
that everyone thought he couldn't beat.
I can't base it on facts, but...
...I think he may beat the Evo Iv, too.
I don'! know why, but Pm
suddenly feeling hopeful.
RighLTakumi?
I never thought an Eight-Six
could race this well.
The downhill battle is so deep.
So fast...
What a fast car that is!
I just don't understand one thing, Keisuke.
Yeah'!
Even if he sticks like super glue,
how can he pass the Evo IV
with his inferior Eight-Six'!
I understand that downhill
minimizes the power difference,
but it can never make
the Eight-Six more powerful.
He's slower on the straightaways,
and since they're equally skilled,
it's almost impossible
for him to get ahead at a corner.
If he can't get ahead, he'll lose.
Just wait. I don't need to explain it.
What's about to happen right there
is the answer to your question.
I don'! get it.
He can'! get ahead.
It': impossible!
He shortens the gap right
before we enter each corner.
Bu! it's partly because my from
tires have lost some pressure.
It': an Eight-Six, after all.
It has slow acceleration.
I can always pull away after a tum.
It pays to be in from, Kyoichi.
Unless I make a stupid mistake, this race is...
...100% mine.
He': fast.
He's the fastest I've seen,
as far as acceleration after a turn is concerned.
I can'! stick with him. He has too much power.
I've never felt this way before.
Even with the "ditch" tum, Pm falling behind.
To offset my slow acceleration,
I have to exit comers at a much
higher speed than he does.
Then I can catch him before the next comer.
I guess I have to do what I did
against Ryosuke Takahashi.
The Ditch Tum No. 2...
...for faster exit acceleration.
The comer before the bridge is the place.
Can I catch the ditch correctly
if! charge in at top speed?
I have one chance!
Pm different tonight.
They're close!
They're just around the corner.
Honestly...
...I'm not 100% sure if he
can actually pass the Evo IV.
I just want to believe
that no one can beat him...
...when my brother couldn't.
Don'! lose!
I won'! forgive you if you lose
to anyone before our rematch.
The Eight-Six is behind!
NOW!
I won! This is the end.
He disappeared.
What the heck?!
He caught the Evo IV at the turn': exit.
What happened?!
It's over.
He got inside.
How?! Wsjust an old junker,
so how can it be so fast?!
Damn, I can't control the tires.
Damn it!
What an incredible race!
What will happen next'!
Nothing. It's over.
It was over when he moved next
to the Evo IV before this turn.
There's no way to pass him now.
Man, he showed him up big time.
You're unreal, Takumi Fujiwara.
--The Eight-Six is in front!
--He won!
Akina's Eight-Six has stopped
Team Emperor's sweep!
Unbelievable. He beat the Ian-Evo.
It's creepy.
I don'! feel like I won. Because it': Akina?
I knew exactly where to attack
and when to use the "ditch" tum.
I would've lost anywhere else.
Sorry, Kyoichi.
Do you have any idea why I'm mad, Seiji'!
Do you think you can explain
why you lost this race'!
No, I don't. I just couldn't shake him off.
I don't know how that slow
Eight-Six could keep up with me,
or what kind of technique he used.
Of course not.
How could you see anything
in the rearview mirror'!
You could've observed
much more from behind.
"Simulation 3" was for that very reason.
Had you listened to me,
you wouldn't have suffered an ugly loss.
Stop acting like a stupid monkey
and start using your head!
I apologize.
What do we do now, Kyoichi'!
Our plan to sweep Gunma is no more.
But regret won't erase this defeat.
We'll suck it up and head to Akagi next.
The Red Suns'!
My ultimate target is Ryosuke Takahashi.
If we win in Akagi, I'll be satisfied.
I just have to win.
What about the Eight-Six, Kyoichi'!
We have our pride.
We can't just accept the defeat.
Shut up! You don't have to tell me that!
Just leave him to me.
Pm the one who is the most upset about this.
That was so satisfying last night!
I've never felt that satisfied before.
I remember the Evo IV guy with the ponytail
trashed us at the lake by saying,
"An Eight-Six racer isn't worthy of my time."
lwish I could just rub it in his face.
Right, Takumi'! Wasn't it satisfying?
It wasn't satisfying.
What'! Why not?
I've had this vague thought lately,
but it became clear last night.
I don't like racing in Akina.
--I'm done racing here.
--Yeah, right.
When you think, nothing good comes out of it.
What's wrong with Akina'!
I don't think I won the race last night.
I actually feel like I lost.
Hold on,Takumi! Why are you upset'!
I'm not upset.
Declaring my plans to you does no good,
but I'm done with Akina.
I've decided to race elsewhere,
even if it means a defeat.
Again?
There you are. Hey, Takumi!
Big news! Akagi will be hot this weekend!
Team Emperor and the Red Suns are facing off!
We can't miss that!
Rumor has it the guy with the black Ian-Evo
is racing for Team Emperor.
Ryosuke Takahashi will race for the Red Suns!
Hey, Takumi, are you listening to me'!
Hey! What's the matter, Takumi'!
Nothing.
When Takumi looks spaced out,
that means he's thinking
about something, right, ltsuki'!
That's actually very rare.
Most of the time, he's just spaced out
and not thinking about anything.
Which one is it today'!
I have no idea, but he's acting weird today.
--A black Evo Ill!
--Is that him'!
--It's him!
--Emperor!
Why don't you come to Akagi'!
Come to Akagi and race me.
A challenge!
No. But you guys probably don't get it.
Do you still remember what
I said to you by the lake'!
You're talented,
but you have no chance as
long as you drive an Eight-Six.
That's what I said.
I can show you what I meant by that.
If you race me, you'll see things
you didn't realize before.
Come to Akagi today or tomorrow, if you like.
I'll give you a preliminary race
before facing the Red Suns.
Unlike the Akina races you're used to,
it'll be a quick defeat for you.
But in that quick race,
you may learn something new.
If you understand me, come to Akagi.
That's all I wanted to say.
What nonsense! Who does he think he is'!
You don't have to go there, Takumi.
I know that.
He acted all cool,
but I bet hejust wants revenge in Akagi.
I bet he does!
But I've decided not to race in Akina anymore.
What'!
If Akagi weren't crowded for
the Emperor-Red Suns challenge,
--| would probably go.
--Takumi!
I hate for him to think that
I chickened out, but I'll pass.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I saw it, Bunta.
I saw your son race in Akina.
Considering how good he already is,
this engine will be gone soon.
It'll be sooner than later.
What are you gonna do'!
You said you wouldn't
replace it until he lost a race.
I wasn't planning on him lasting this long.
He just refuses to lose.
Will the engine blow first, or will he lose first'!
Either way, the new one is ready to go.
That note...
"Mashed Magi.
She': dating an older man in a Mercedes...
What the hell was that, then?
Hello'!
So, there's no way you'll change your mind'!
No.
A family restaurant near Maebashi?
Do you really want me to go? Fine.
Dad, I need to run an errand.
Okay.
I can'! get this out of my head.
The more I try to forget it, the more
I think about it and get irritated.
Maybe I like Magi that much.
So...
...it's silly, but just this once, H! fall for it.
This is it.
A Mercedes.
Papa,thank you for
understanding my selfishness.
How's it going, Seiji'!
I'm more than ready to go.
I already have a strategy for this course.
It was kind of annoying to
see the Red Suns' lackeys
timing me at every check point.
Ignore them.
As long as you know the course perfectly,
the strategy's basically the same for any pass.
By the way, do you think he'll come'!
Who knows'!
I would say there's about
a 40% chance he'll show up.
It's more convenient for us if he comes.
The truth is that I want to be
done with these little chores
--before I face Ryosuke Takahashi.
--Yeah.
Our ultimate goal is to conquer all of Gunma.
Once I defeat Ryosuke,
we're done with Gunma.
But I can't sleep well at night
knowing that we let one escape in Akina.
Hopefully, I can destroy the
Eight-Six in a warm-up race
and go into the main event refreshed.
That was him that just headed up.
What's he doing in Akagi'!
Furikaereba itsudatte
Kawaranu kimi no egao ga aim
Arukitsukare tachidomaru hi mo
Chiisa nu yorokobi no hi mo
Kono ryoute ni kakaekirenai
Al' wo oshiete kureta
Atatakaku
Sotto yasashiku yomigaeru kaze wa
{ma hitori sora wo
Mitsumeteru boku ni hohoendeiru
Mada ano hi no mama no
Mabushisa de te wo futteiru
Kimi wa everlasting memory
Takumi storms to Akagi!
A fierce battle against the Evo H!
unfolds before the Takahashi
Brothers, and the result?
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"Countdown to Destruction."
Don'! miss it!