Information, it': an era
where it travels in a second
Bu! you don'! know what
choice you should take
"Money can'! buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don'! realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can'! even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get moved!
Let': move into the brand new world
Let': dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let': warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That': our law!
He hasn't changed a bit.
"Act 1:The Ultimate Tofu Store Drift"
Even the 1991 model costs 1.3 million yen.
The S13 is expensive.
Like I thought, it's gotta be the Eight-Six.
The Eight-Six is a real possibility.
Anyway, the car has to be FR. Right, Takumi'!
Takumi!
Hey! Are you listening?
I'm listening, ltsuki.
So how much is this Eight-Six'!
Well, this one is 300,000 yen...
...but it hasn't passed inspection.
How much have you saved so far'!
About 50,000 yen.
You've got along way to go.
Yeah... Yeah...
Isn't there any way to make
a lot of quick money?!
With our current part-time
jobs at the gas station,
even if we work full-time
during summer break,
we'll only make 120,000 yen at most.
There's gotta be a betterjob out there.
You guys are working part-time'!
M0gi...?
What'! Is it so strange that I'm talking to you'!
Not really...
You said you could get 120,000
working full-time this summer.
How many hours are you
supposed to work every day'!
From early in the morning till late at night.
What?!
You can only make 120,000
a month for that much work?!
That's about right...
Wages for high school students are really low!
I didn't know...
I've never had a part-time job...
Good luck with your job!
Let's get together after finals!
Sure!
She just said, "Let's get together!" didn't she'!
--Yeah.
--Go out with Mogi?!
Good! Good!
Takumi, why didn't you tell me'!
--You should have told me you're Mogi': friend.
--| haven't talked with her in about a year.
We were in the same club.
We talked a lot until last summer.
What are you talking about?
Who cares about that'!
Natsuki Mogi...! What a great turn of events!
I've been checking her out
for a while... She's so cute...
Takumi! Hey,Takumi! Quit zoning out!
If we don't hurry, we'll be in big trouble!
We've got a grammar test next class!
Wait up!
Hey, why don't we buy an Eight-Six together?!
If we combine our money,
we can afford the loan.
No way.
Why do you want a car that badly'!
Your family already has a car, right?
It's no good.
My old man's car is an automatic
and front-wheel drive.
And it's a diesel. It's crap.
I wouldn't even call it a car...
It has four tires and it runs. It's a car.
You just don't get it.
If it's not fun on the mountain pass,
you can't call it a car.
What do you do on the mountain?
What do you think?! We're going
to challenge the corners!
Challenge the corners...'!
Is that fun'!
Of course it's fun!
You're a guy and you don't
want to tackle the corners?!
I'm already tired of that kind of stuff.
What'! What do you mean'!
We just got our licenses last month.
You look cute.
That outfit always looks great on you.
Really? Thank you, Papa.
You know, Papa, one of my
classmates is working part-time.
He says even if he works all summer,
he'll only earn 120,000 yen.
Well, that's about right.
It's hard earning money, isn't it'!
You spend more than that on me in a month.
Is it really all right to spend so much on me'!
Of course. You're worth it.
Really?
I don't understand...
--Thank you very much!
Hey, Takumi! Please think
about the Eight-Six deal.
I don't care about an Eight-Six!
You kids have good taste...
...trying to get an Eight-Six.
See'! See'! lketani thinks so too, right?!
Yeah, the Eight-Six is a good car.
I told you.
But I...
To be honest, I don't know
what an Eight-Six is.
Who makes it'!
Are you serious, Takumi?
Want to drink some high octane?
Working at a gas station and
you don't know the Eight-Six?!
What a disgrace!
Oh, well. It's no surprise.
When the Nine-Two model came out,
you guys werejust in 2nd or 3rd grade.
We have an old car at my house,
but we just use it for our deliveries.
You can't compare that to an Eight-Six!
Even if it's old, the Eight-Six is special!
When we buy an Eight-Six,
will you let us join your team'!
I've always dreamed of joining
the Akina Speed Stars.
Sure! Oh, by the way...
It's Saturday, so everyone is
meeting at Mt. Akina tonight.
You guys wanna come along?
What?! Can we'!
But we don't have a car...
I'll give you a ride.
We can ride in your S13?!
I'll go! I'll go! I'm definitely going!
You're going too. Right, Takumi?
This is a rare opportunity!
--Um, I never said I wanted to go.
--Cool! I can meet the whole team!
Excuse us.We're going home!
All right! I'll pick you up
at the bus stop at 8 PM.
Okay!
You're really into it.
Which mountain are you going to'!
Boss, Mt. Akina is the only mountain
around here worth racing on.
We're the fastest team on Mt. Akina.
Many claim that they're
the fastest on Mt. Akina.
When I was still racing,
there was a guy that everyone
admitted was the fastest.
And he's still driving on Mt. Akina.
Still?!
I know all the racers at Akina...
...but none of them are that old.
It's just because he drives during
a different time. Because...
...he's now the owner of a tofu shop.
What'!
About 4 o'clock in the morning,
he delivers his tofu to the hotels at Lake Akina.
It's amazing to watch his downhill speed.
Because it's his business,
he makes the run every day,
even in the rain and snow.
He knows even the smallest stain
on the asphalt on Mt. Akina.
I'd even bet on it.
The fastest downhill car on Mt. Akina...
...is the Eight-Six from the tofu shop.
The Eight-Six from the tofu shop?!
"Green Shopping Street"
Going out, Takumi?
Yeah. I have plans with ltsuki.
I don't care if you're out at night,
but I'll drag you out of bed if you
don't wake up in the morning.
You don't need to remind me.
I'm going.
Shut up,Takumi!
You're ruining lketani': concentration.
Whatever! But this sucks, and I'm scared!
No big deal. Everyone gets scared
when they ride with a street racer.
Next, we'll take the hairpin in second gear!
You're still too noisy, Takumi!
All right.Tonight, I'm going all out.
Are you all right, Takumi?
I didn't think you'd get that scared...
I was in the mood and
pushed the car quite a bit.
You're a wimp,Takumi! Shame on you!
You're the type who screams
on roller coasters, aren't you?!
I've never thought that
roller coasters are scary.
It's not like that...
ltsuki, even if I explained it to you,
you'd never understand...
...this fear...
What'!
I've never seen them before...
They're headed for Mt. Akina
at this time of the night?
Something may happen
on the mountain tonight.
We've got visitors.
The Red Suns?
Are they the Red Suns,
the fastest drivers in Akagi?
We're the members of
the Akagi Red Suns Team.
I don't want to be rude, but...
Who's the fastest team, or driver,
on this mountain? Please tell us.
--What do they want'!
--We're the fastest.
We're the Akina Speed Stars Team.
We consider ourselves the fastest here.
Then we've found what we're looking for!
Would you like to hold a practice session
with our team, the Akagi Red Suns,
here at Mt. Akina?
"What?
--Are they serious?
Wow! What a great turn of events!
What do you think'!
Since we usually only run with people
we know, it's becoming routine.
Running against other teams
gives us a new challenge.
We can make new friends
and exchange knowledge.
And it improves our skills, too.
At first, we can run together.
Then each team will be
represented by one driver
to compete in both uphill and downhill.
We aren't concerned about winning or losing.
We only seek to develop
friendship between the teams.
What do you think'!
--If you put it that way, how can we refuse?
--Okay.
How about next Saturday at 10 o'clock'!
Okay, fine.
Today, we'll just take it easy.
Awesome! This is awesome, Takumi!
We don't need to be intimidated!
--We're going, too!
--Yeah!
lketani!
Let me watch the Takahashi Brothers--
people call them the fastest in Akagi!
You mean the Takahashi Brothers,
the famous street racers who've
been featured in the magazines?
Yes.They're also known
as "The Rotary Brothers."
lketani! What about us?!
Sorry.When I make a serious run,
I don't take passengers.
Wait here. I'll pick you up later.
This sucks! Why're we the
only ones without a car'!
Hey, ltsuki...
Is it that much fun to be a street racer'!
I don't get it...
Why does everyone get so excited about it'!
I'm the one who doesn't get it!
We can hear the sound of cars
running hard one after another, right'!
Why can't you get excited about it, Takumi?!
Excited?
Hello, Fujiwara Tofu Shop...
Oh, it's just you.
What a surprise...
Just me'!
I haven't talked to you in so long,
and this is the greeting I get'!
The other day, you passed me on
your way back from a delivery.
I signaled, but you ignored me.
Nope, it wasn't me.
It had to be you. It was your Eight-Six.
Well, I mean...
...it was my car, but I wasn't driving it.
My son Takumi delivers tofu to the hotels now.
What did you say?!
Since when?!
Five years ago.
Five years ago'! Since he
was in the seventh grade'!
Damn! I can't keep up with them at all!
They're fast! I'm at my limit,
but I can'! keep up with any of the Red Suns.
What do you think, brother?
They're all trash.
Even our second string can easily beat them.
We don't need to bring
the top drivers next week.
I'll pass.
If you're not gonna come, I guess I'll pass, too.
No, you should run.
You should set a record for this course
which the locals can never break.
Otherwise, the name of the Akagi Red Suns
will never become legendary.
Yeah...
First, we'll set new records for
every course in this prefecture.
Then we'll take Saitama,
Kanagawa,Tokyo, and Chiba.
We'll have every record
in the entire Kanto region,
then we'll become legends,
and then we'll retire.
That is the Akagi Red Suns'
"Fastest in Kanto Project."
They're incredible.
They are completely different from us.
I'm totally shocked that we got
so beaten on our home ground.
They've put serious money into their
suspensions, and they've got power, too.
There's no way we can
compete with the Red Suns.
But how can we avoid a
challenge on our own turf'!
That's right! We can't back out now!
But guts alone won't beat those guys.
I know that... But...!
It's getting late.
Let's get together tomorrow and talk about it.
Street racers don't like losing.
They get too serious about racing.
There's nothing worse than losing to
outsiders on your own home ground.
It's like a law for street racers.
Where's Ryosuke'!
He went home a while ago.
We're the only ones still here.
It's almost dawn.
I guess we should head back, too.
If I get serious, they can't keep up with me.
They're still at that level...
Finally caught up, huh'!
That's not one of ours.
Is that an MR2 or a 180'!
Nice driving. But after two corners,
I won't even see you in my mirror.
An Eight-Six?!
You've gotta be kidding!
My FD can't outrun an old Eight-Six?!
Is this some sort of nightmare?! Crap!
I'm the No. 2 driver of the Akagi Red Suns!
Doesn't he know this road?
After this slow right, there': a sharp left.
If he doesnW'. slow down, he'll be in the ravine!
I knew it! He's going too fast!
There's no more room to slow down!
What the hell?!
Inertia drift?!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
$0 HO one IHTQFVQHQS
Never stop, I don't want to stop
Even if you cry because of a sacrificed love
Aim for the peak, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! The warning chime is so cheap!
The sheep should clear the road
'Cuz Pm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy motivation is total stimulation
You tried to escape,
but anywhere is a safety zone
Something is within your grasp
and something is forgotten
Even if the world ends it will never change
Beasty shout, no one can touch you
Cross over now to the time of an intense dream
Rage your dream, split the darkness
Like a streak to the peak
Erase the freezing darkness worldwide
Rage your dream, and open the road
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
A point 01 second knockdown
Reverberations left behind,
disappear to the next town
The losers are left in the dust
Let': ignore the constraints of logic
'Cause theyWe a pain
A streaker runs naked across the street
Something they would know
Rage your dream,
continue on the unending road
Don'! look back on your love or your past
Go forward and you'll shine brightly
Rage your dream, you're living in the now
Drift fans and Eight-Six owners!
Thanks for waiting!
At last it begins!
Initial D!
What did you think of
Takumi': super drift technique,
racing his 1.6 liter non-turbo Eight-Six
against a high-potential 350HP FD?!
Pretty cool, don'! you think?
And for those who understand
all the technicaljargon,
initial D shows you the essential details!
Next time, get ready to watch
another exciting race!
Don'! miss it!