"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let': look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let': go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
it': the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let': look for explosive thrills, it': the time!
"Act 7: Battle at Akagi!
The Black and White Flash!"
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
No Eight-Six.
I feel like I've lost something important,
like a family member.
Hey!
You look perfectly half-asleep, as usual.
It's too early to be acting so hyper, ltsuki.
Why are you so excited?
Why else?!
Today is the day the Red Suns
and the Emperors square off!
I'm already so nervous that I can't even go pee.
We should carpool like we did
when we went to Myogi.
I'm wondering if we can take your Eight-Six.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
I said I was wondering if we
could take your Eight-Six...
Hey, wait up,Takumi!
Anyway, I'm so excited about tonight's race!
Any predictions?
I predict that Ryosuke
Takahashi is going to win.
I don't think the Emperors' Sudo is that good.
He just drives a better car.
Stop talking about things
you don't understand.
Why are you mad'!
It's not that I'm mad.
Something came up,
so I can't go to Akagi with you tonight.
Why not?!
I just can't, so go with lketani and Kenji.
--What?! Ta ku mi lost?
--Yes.
He really did go to Akagi last night.
Rumor has it that his Eight-Six
stopped during the race.
Stopped?
Do you mean it's damaged,
or that he blew the engine?
We don't exactly know what really happened.
We're all panicking here.
We thought you might know
something about it, boss.
Takumi's dad is your friend.
Sorry, I don't know anything.
Hang on. I'll call him.
He isn't answering.
Takumi': probably at school, too.
It's very irritating that we don't know.
Hey! It's Keisuke Takahashi.
Is Takumi Fujiwara here'!
He's off today.
I see. I was hoping I could talk to him directly.
I have a message for him.
Last night's race doesn't count.
I don't accept it.
It was too strange to be considered a race.
I don't know what others think of it,
but I don't agree that
Takumi Fujiwara was defeated.
One more thing.
We will avenge his Eight-Six.
We will be happy to break the
conceited Emperor's nose for him.
Later.
We'll give him the message.
Good luck with tonight's battle.
We'll be rooting for you.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
What?!
Not good!
Hey!
Itsuki... don't you think
this rock is a little too big'!
You could've broken the window.
I looked for smaller ones,
but I couldn't find any.
I figured it would be okay if I threw it lightly.
It's not okay!
You would've broken the glass for sure.
Oh, sorry!
I didn't do it on purpose!
I guess I deserved it...
I told you that I wasn't going to Akagi.
I know. I decided not to go, either.
Instead, I was going to Akina Pass for a drive.
Wanna come along?
Hey,Takumi'!
I'm sorry about this morning.
I didn't know.
I don't care about that,
but you heard about last night already?
I heard it from lketani after school.
They know, too, then.
Yeah, I hear everyone in
town is talking about it.
Everyone notices you.
By the way, lketani told me
to give you this message.
Hey,this car is right on my tail.
He's probably going to see tonight's race.
I guess so...
...but he's making me nervous
because he's so close to me.
I'll speed up a little.
He's trying to pass us.
You should let him.
What's he driving?
What?!
An Eight-Six Levin!
With turbo!
I heard the waste gate pass the exhaust gas!
He passed my SR-20 turbo like it was parked!
Unbelievable!This is uphill, too!
Where did he come from?
Have I seen that Eight-Six around here?
Keisuke Takahashi came to
the gas station and told them
that he doesn't think you lost last night's race.
I don't know what he means by that.
I did lose, because I was
completely outmatched.
The Emperors' Sudo was really that good'!
He was. I would've lost to him even in Akina.
I see.
So how is the Eight-Six'!
You can fix it, right'!
My dad thinks it needs a new engine.
"What?
--| shouldn't have gone to Akagi.
I'm regretting it big time.
The air is full of tension.
Did you hear about last night'!
Yeah. Akina': Eight-Six lost, right'!
I hear that Kyoichi Sudo':
technique is beyond belief.
I guess Ryosuke Takahashi
is Gunma': last hope.
I want him to win no matter what.
So, Shingo, you came to see the battle, too'!
Hey, Takeshi.
I figured I would root for the Red Suns tonight.
Ryosuke Takahashi won't lose.
We can't have the Ian-Evo
squad looking down on Gunma.
Yeah... Hey!
We're too close again. Let's keep our distance.
An Eight-Six!
--Akina's Eight-Six'!
--No way, it has a Saitama plate.
This is a good spot, Kazumi.
Yeah.
Here comes the Ian-Evo squad!
Good luck, Red Suns!
Do you have anything to say, Ryosuke'!
Not really.
Tonight's battle only involves you and me.
That's more like it.
Let's start a real race, shall we'!
Remember, you told me
that you wouldn't race in Akina anymore?
When I heard that,
I thought you were so brave.
Your wanting to race elsewhere impressed me.
Wrong!
It wasn't like that last night.
Something awful happened and I was furious.
I was so mad that I didn't
know what I was doing.
That's why I ruined the car.
It was probably a punishment.
I shouldn't have been racing a
car when I was feeling like that.
I know that now.
I can accept the loss,
because I wasn't good enough.
But I can't stop regretting
destroying my dad's precious car.
Takumi...
What's the strategy, Kyoichi'!
Simulation X.
"X"? Do we have an "X"?
Ryosuke is an exception.
It's a special strategy for this battle.
I'll win with Simulation X.
I'm starting the countdown!
Five...
Four... Three...
Two... One...
Gog
As long as my brother runs his normal race,
he won'! lose to that Ian-Evo.
What sharp cornering by Ryosuke Takahashi!
How odd! Ryosuke usually lets
his opponent take the lead.
What will happen next'!
Awesome! Both cars are so intense!
This race is so thrilling.
Can you see their subtle strategies, Kazumi'!
What'!
The Evo Ill had a quick start,
but he didn't fully accelerate.
When they entered the first
corner all tangled up,
it seemed to me that the
Evo Ill retreated a little.
Perhaps the Evo Ill chose to stay behind
as part of some strategy.
It was worth coming to Akagi
to be able to see a race like this.
I can win. I can win this race!
By staying behind,
I can see what Ryosuke is trying to do.
I've got him.
All the uncertainties in my head are gone now.
I haven'! forgotten it, Ryosuke.
What you told me a year ago...
...after I lost to you.
Don't let this go to your head!
I still don't accept street racers.
They're all mediocre racers!
The motor sport technique developed
to achieve maximum speed
can't be inferior to primitive street technique!
That's what I believe.
You can believe what you want,
but the mountain pass
requires its own technique.
You won't succeed with just
the technique you learned
at Gymkhana and other circuits.
That can't possibly be right!
KYOichi!
I don't intend to continue this
fruitless conversation with you.
It won't lead to an answer.
If you believe your theory
is right, then defeat me.
If you can't, then it's just a theory.
I won'! forget this.
H! defeat you,
and make you taste this same anguish.
I haven'! forgotten it, Ryosuke.
I know you know it, too.
All of our racing theories and personal beliefs
are riding on this race tonight.
Ryosuke...
You said the mountain pass
requires its own technique.
The boldness to take the shortest line...
wheel and toe...
...and the all-wheel drift
with zero countersteering.
You sure are fast.
But what': so special about your technique?
You're merely using circuit racing technique!
If you seek speed,
you'll end up having to rely
on motor sport technique!
My theory is right!
Ryosuke': FC is moving smoothly.
The Evo Ill is right with him.
Here they come! Who's ahead'!
The FC or the Evo Ill'!
It's the FC!
I'll show you how much I've
grown since last year, Ryosuke!
This is where my 4WD and
the misfiring system excel!
What?! The Evo Ill passed
Ryosuke Takahashi': FC!
Whenever I turned around
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
The warm wind
Comes back quietly and tenderly
And as I gaze at the sky alone
You smile down upon me
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory
The Eight-Six is running again?!
The Eight-Six was seen in Akina!
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"Dangerous Car."
Don'! miss it!