"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let': look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let': go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
it': the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let': look for explosive thrills, it': the time!
"An amazing downhill specialist
came out ofAkina's mountain passes.
Driving his cherished Eight-Six,
this young genius stunned all
with his amazing drift technique.
Since the beginning of junior high school,
Takumi has been driving
through the mountain passes
making deliveries for his family's tofu store.
It was all part of his father Bunta': plan
to nurture Takumi': talent
and make him a racing genius.
Driving every day, through rain and snow,
he gradually acquired and
perfected his remarkable skills.
He emerged as a hero and
the fastest man in Gunma,
and all the racers in the area
started to challenge him.
Takumi improved with every race...
His driving amazed the spectators
and captured their hearts.
In the end, he even defeated
the great Ryosuke Takahashi,
and the glorious legend of the
invincible downhill racer was born.
But there was no rest for
this warrior of the road.
There were more battles ahead
for this fastest downhill racer."
Darn it! There's no way I'll let
an outsider mess with me!
This is a piece of cake.
Whoa!
--He passed him!
--Oh, no! That Evo IV is fast!
Darn it!
"Act 1: A New Threat"
It's just like what fighter pilots used to do
when they shot down other fighters.
Quite fancy, isn't it'!
In a month, we, Team Emperor, will rule Gunma.
Ian-Evo drivers are the true
kings of the mountain passes.
--Hey, Takumi.
--Yeah'!
As I get used to it, I really think
that my Eight-Five is
pathetically slow on the uphill.
I want more power.
Really?
I've secretly been thinking of adding
a turbocharger to my Eight-Five
and turning it into a super-fast car!
Turbo? Can you add that now'!
Isn't it supposed to come
with the car when you buy it'!
I know. But there's this thing
called a "bolt-on turbo."
You can add it later if you want to.
Turbo is the easiest way to add
power to your car, isn't it'!
Imagine my Eight-Five with a turbocharger...
...going as fast as drivers
in an S13 or One-Eighty...
...on a straight course!
I bet everyone would be stunned!
Just thinking about it is exciting! Hooray!
Move over, ltsuki. Someone':
coming up really fast.
What...'!
Hey! The other way!
"That's a Ian-Evo!
--A Ian-Evo'!
What': up with that car?
What a strange movement!
Did you see that insane acceleration?!
--Yeah.
--The engine is only 2000 cc...
...but it's got 280 horsepower.
That's the power of turbo.
It's also got four-wheel drive.
I see. That movement comes
from the four-wheel drive.
Four tires can handle power that two tires can't.
My Evo IV is so beautiful
that it gives me chills.
This is an example
of what the pursuit of perfect
driving functionality leads to.
It's like the body of a well-trained boxer.
The air ducts on the front...
Protruding blister packing...
The oversized rear wing...
They all have their purpose.
The Ian-Evo was developed and perfected
to win world-class rally tournaments.
High-powered turbo and four-wheel drive.
A car isn't complete without them.
The Ian-Evo is the fastest street racer.
Hey, Kyoichi. Let's finish
all the FR punks in Gunma.
That Ian-Evo is here.
I don't like this.
Do you think they're from some racing team'!
Don't worry about them.
I'm gonna get some coffee.You want some'!
Oh, me, too! Please!
He's coming this way!
Hey!
I need directions.
Uh, okay!
This route is much shorter.
I see.Thanks a lot.
By the way, let me ask you something.
Who's the fastest driver here in Akina'!
The fastest?
Did you by any chance come here
to challenge the Eight-Six'!
What, us'! Challenging an Eight-Six'!
Your face is enough of a joke, Levin boy.
Defeating an Eight-Six
will not impress anyone.
Worse than that.
My teammates would laugh at me
if I bragged about such a thing.
Anyone driving a junker like
an Eight-Six is beneath me!
I wouldn't race them even if they asked.
You shouldn't talk like that...
...when you've never even
seen Akina': Eight-Six!
Akina': Eight-Six has never lost!
Not to an FC! Not to an FD...
...not even to an R32!
Oh, really? They all must have
been really bad drivers, then.
Not at all! They were all the
top drivers in this prefecture!
Oh, no!
The top'! It's pretty low-level
here in Gunma, isn't it'!
What did you just say?!
Stop it, ltsuki!
You, too, Seiji.
You don't have to talk like that.
We didn't come here to pick fights.
Sorry, guys. My buddy here has a big mouth.
No problem.
I'll just say this so you won't misunderstand.
We don't mean to insult that Eight-Six driver.
I am sure his technique is great.
But the car...
I'd have to say the Eight-Six
is no longer good enough.
He's right! Tell that to the driver.
And tell him that we might let him race us
if he drives a more powerful car.
But we will never lose.
The king of mountain passes is the Len-Eve!
Darn! Hey,Takumi!
Aren't you mad at all after all that talk?!
Yeah, I was pretty angry.
So why didn't you say anything?!
Watching you get furious...
...somehow calmed me down.
What the heck is up with that'!
Besides, there have been guys
who talked like that before, right'!
--Right...
--Arguing with them doesn't do any good.
You can't really tell who's faster
unless you actually race.
I see your point.
But I can't just stand there when
someone insults the Eight-Six like that!
Because I've always admired the Eight-Six.
I know the Eight-Six is an old model.
It's got no turbo, and it's slow on the uphill.
But in the true fan's mind,
the Eight-Six is faster than any other car!
Hey, stop crying. Here you go.
What'!
Drink your coffee.
Thanks.
Hey, Takumi.You can do it, right'!
You can beat the Ian-Evo on a downhill,
and crush the ego of that
cocky long-haired guy!
I don't know. He said he
wouldn't race the Eight-Six.
--I've got it... The turbo!
"What?
If we added turbo to the Eight-Six,
it would be amazing,Takumi!
This Ian-Evojerk certainly sounds obnoxious.
Yeah. I was so furious!
I wonder if they're the guys who
came to challenge Thunder Fire'!
They're members of a team
called Emperor or something.
I heard they're from Nikko
and they only drive Ian-Evos,
and that they're extremely cocky,
but they drive very fast.
I heard they beat Thunder Fire into the ground.
I heard about that, too.
They supposedly said that
they wanted to rule Gunma,
so they might show up in Akina.
Are you serious?!
I wonder if they were checking
out the area yesterday?
The Ian-Evo will be really hard to beat...
...even for Ta ku m I's Eig ht-S ix.
Thank you very much!
Anyway, putting these guys aside,
we never know when or who
he'll be racing from now on.
So because of that,
we definitely need to beef up his Eight-Six.
Right?! Right?!
That's what I'm talking about!
Adding turbo to the Eight-Six.
That's a good idea!
I mean, good for ltsuki.
It might be easier for him to just
switch to a faster car, of course.
But I just can't imagine him driving
anything other than the Eight-Six.
Yeah.We want him to stick to the Eight-Six.
You're both so right!
The coolest part is that he drives
the Eight-Six and he's darn fast!
Takumi, give it some thought.
I don't know...
It's my father's car, you know.
That's right, I forgot...
Can't we somehow convince your father?
I've got it! If we told him
we'd pay for everything,
I bet he wouldn't object!
You're right! I bet he'd love
having his car souped up!
How about it,Takumi'!!
If the car were more powerful,
its fuel economy would suffer, right'!
Yeah, sort of.
Then we've got no chance.
Because my dad is stingy as hell.
Don't say things like that
to spoil our image of him!
Your dad is our idol, you know!
What?! That man is your idol'!
Hey..-
You shouldn't waste time
trying to convince him.
We should just go ahead
with the "Akina Eight-Six
Power-Up Project" ourselves!
Right! Let's do it!
Long time no see, Ryosuke.
Kyoichi Sudo. I thought it was you.
What are you up to'!
Easy, now! You should be nicer,
seeing as how we haven't
seen each other in over a year.
We're bored because we don't have
anyone to play with in our hood.
So we came looking for some
high-spirited playmates, that's all.
Since this will be our playground,
we thought we'd say hi
to the people here today.
How considerate of you. Do as you wish.
But here in Akagi,
the playtime won't be as fun as you think...
...as long as our team, the Red Suns, is here.
You'rejust as proud as I remember.
But don't forget this...
I'm not the same person I was a year ago.
You beat me last time, but now it's my turn!
Just as you broke my perfect winning record,
I will now break your winning streak!
I'm sorry to tell you, but my streak...
...was broken recently.
What'!
I lost to an Eight-Six on a
downhill course in Akina.
What did you say?!
I was considering retiring,
but I don't want you to
think that I'm running away.
So maybe I'll agree to a rematch
and race you once more.
And I admire your enthusiasm
in coming all the way here.
I'll speak to the other teams
and arrange for the course in Akagi
to be free for three days before the race.
Drive as much as you want and get used to it.
I'll race you whenever you're ready, Kyoichi.
What a jerk, acting all cool like that!
I'll chase him down and tailgate him!
Don't, Seiji.You can't.
You won't be able to catch him.
I won't? Such a skinny, frail guy!
He doesn't look that tough at all.
And that outdated FC...
He even lost to an Eight-Six, right'!
You idiot! Don't underestimate
RyosukeTakahashi!
I was solidly defeated by his FC last year!
The White Comet of Akagi...
I thought I was the only
one who could beat him...
Bu! Ryosuke lost?
He lost to an Eight-Six from Akina?
Akina': Eight-Six has never lost to anyone!
Not to an FC! Not to an FD...
...not even to an R32!
I see. That kid was talking
about that same Eight-Six.
I wonder what the driver': like?
Guess who'!
Cut it out, Mogi.
I'm actually relieved.
I don't know what I would have done
if you had said some other girl's name.
Silly...
Hey, Takumi, let's go home.
Oh, maybe I'll go home alone.
After all, I am the lonely driver.
Yeah. So, I should go home alone...
--The "Eight-Six Power-Up Project." --What are
you talking about? We have to work today.
I have something to do, too.
Okay.
See you, Takumi. Bye!
Bye.
So, Takumi...
...how far have you two gone since then'!
How fa r'!
Oh, come on!
You and Natsuki! Have you
gone farther than kissing?
Come on, tell me! Whoops!
This is a one-race match.
It'll be decided by a hill climb.
--Fine.
--Shall we begin, then'!
Are you ready, Seiji'!
Anytime!
Don'! mess this upJakeshi.
Show them the willpower of Gunma drivers!
Just for today, H! root for you!
Our goal is much more than this race.
Seiji, don'! waste time goofing around here.
Five seconds to the start!
Four... Three...
Two... One...
Gog
Wait and see.
Compared to a Ian-Evo, an R32 is just a toy.
I'll show you the difference!
You Emperor punks,
or whatever you call yourselves...
...I will defend Gunma!
And you'll be buried deep
at the bottom of Myogi Valley!
Whenever I turned around
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
The warm wind
Comes back quietly and tenderly
And as I gaze at the sky alone
You smile down upon me
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory
If! don't stop them, who will?!
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"Team Emperor on Akin a!"
Anyone who doesn't watch this is beneath me!