"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shim kemuri
Misugita yume no daishou
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi
Akuseru funde gomakasu
Yoru ni kowareta mama
Shisen tsuyoku togarasete
Dare no kimagure kara
Sakai sue mo owarisou de
Break into the night, it': the time
Obieta me o shite lost in the night
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart
Jibun sue mo kizutsukete
Taoreru kurai ni Love me so much
SUbQIQ 0 SUIQIQ Gflfllfl 0
Aisuru koto sue dekitara
Kitto sunao ni naresou
There must be some way to
make Takumi stop daydreaming.
The race is on the 15th,
so we still have one more week.
It's a good thing it's not tomorrow.
Aren't the Red Suns and the
Night Kids racing tomorrow?
That's it!
Take Takumi there and
make him watch their race!
It could be exciting enough
to snap him out of his daydreaming!
That's a good idea.That should do the trick!
He'll have a rude awakening.
"Act 22: Fierce Uphill Battle!"
Hey, Dad, I've been thinking...
About what'!
I raced at Usui Pass the other night.
I thought it would be totally
different from Akina Pass.
But as I drove it...
...I realized that it felt very similar to Akina.
Very good.
Is it'!
Usui is a completely
different course from Akina,
but you ran your usual race on it.
It's about how much "Akina"
you take with you to other courses.
--Good luck with the deliveries.
--Okay.
How much "Akina" I take with me...
I think I sort of understand
what he's trying to say.
I need a nap.
He's completely lost in a daydream.
Okay, let the operation begin!
Hey,Takumi!
Big news! Don't freak out!
The Red Suns and the Night Kids
are battling it out tonight!
--So'!
--What do you mean, "so"?!
Since you're taking on
Ryosuke Takahashi next week,
this race is a must-see!
Okay,then!
Let's take your Eight-Six, since it's a
waste of gas to drive two cars there.
--Mine'!
--I'm getting fired up!
You're excited too, right'!
Right...
I'll meet you at your place at 7:00.
Don't forget to borrow the Eight-Six!
The crowd is huge.
Are Takumi and ltsuki here'!
Not yet.
I sure hope ltsuki was able to pull this off.
Hurry up, Takumi, or we'll miss the race.
We got lost because you didn't
want to take the toll road.
You're too cheap.
Look who's talking.
You're the one who didn't drive to save on gas.
I've never heard of a racer
with no sense of direction...
This must be a side effect of his daydreaming.
I got it.
We really gotta hurry!
You made me wait.
The main character shows up last.
Myogi': ravine is steep, so try not to die.
Enough.Your hands are shaking.
Don't worry, it'll be quick.
No Night Kid can touch me.
Your arrogance could end your life.
Let's go, before the rain starts.
--Yeah.
--An Eight-Six!
Akina': Eight-Six came!
An Eight-Six?
Check out this huge crowd!
Just concentrate on finding them, okay'!
I know...
...but it's hard to spot them in this crowd.
Where should we park'!
What about the top'!
There's a big parking lot.
All right, let's go up, then.
I knew you'd come.
You're getting me fired up.
Eight-Six, I'll show you
how much I've improved.
--An Eight-Six!
--You mean Akina's'!
--Yeah.
--Is it really?
HeyTakumi, is it just me,
or do you think people are looking at us'!
--Yeah.
--What do you mean, "yeah"?!
They totally recognize us.
Akina': Eight-Six is famous now.
They have their eye on you, you know'!
It was a good idea to drive the Eight-Six here.
What are you muttering about?
Okay, come forward!
Forward!
Okay.The road is clear!
I'll count down!
Five... Four...
Three... Two...
One... Go!
Wow! What a fast start!
I know Keisuke will win.
Don'! lose. it': not an option on our turf.
"Takahashi"
It's started.
Rain...
The FD': best weapon is
its high cornering speed.
Don'! forget that, Keisuke.
Takumi'!
Don't you think Myogi Pass
is similar to Akina Pass'!
I don't know.
It seems more like Usui Pass to me.
It's nothing like Usui!
It's no use. He's totally lost,
out in the deepest sea.
Take a good look at it!
It's not as narrow as Usui,
and this uphill is just like Akina's.
I mean the rhythm is similar.
Rhythm...'!
Be careful! An FD is quick around comers.
I never thought anyone could
follow me up Myogi': hill.
He's starting to abuse the steering.
He': trying to speed away.
If he did that on a downhill,
the tires would compress.
They just passed the mid-point.
The R32 is in front...
...but it's very close.
I see.
Tell me one thing...
How did Keisuke look coming out of the turn'!
He was one step slower than Nakazato,
but overall, he seems under
control and very smooth,
unlike Nakazato's aggressive
but inconsistent run.
I got it. Thanks.
You've improved, Keisuke,
to be able to race like that.
The R32 is in front.Very tight!
They just passed me.
Nakazato is barely in front.
It sounds like Takeshi is doing well.
He's been training hard.
He became a different person
after losing to the Eight-Six.
I've always considered Takeshi
to be my enemy. But now...
Knowing that he's fighting for
our pride, I feel the camaraderie.
I've never felt this way before.
The R32': in the lead!
Win,Takeshi! I'm counting on you!
I can hear the squeals, but I can't see them.
What'!
Rain...
Oh, no! They're battling at full speed!
It's most dangerous
when it first starts raining.
The rain lifts up the dirt and oil on
the surface and makes it slippery.
They could easily crash.
Raindrops...
Darn, couldn't it have waited?
I gotta be alert.
I could lose control without warning.
It's really coming down.
I hope they don't stop the race.
--Hey, ltsuki'!
--Yeah'!
Since that's the finish line,
this must be the last corner, right'!
Yeah.
That's the highest point in Myogi Pass,
so this is a downhill corner.
The only downhill corner.
Here they come!
This is it!
That': suicidal! You'll crash
into the wall at that speed!
I know! can do this!
My FD': telling me I can!
They're coming at us!
The FD won!
I'm so impressed!
Man, Keisuke Takahashi is good!
This is the first time that I
was inspired by other racers.
Seeing a great race like
that makes me restless.
You got lucky, Keisuke Takahashi.
No, it was skill.
What'!
The last corner was downhill,
so I knew it would come
down to the front tires.
You couldn't quite control them
because they were too compressed.
I kept up my speed,
but maintained the tire pressure.
It was skill.
You did it, Keisuke!
Should we do a downhill race'!
We can't keep going in this rain.
"Right.
--Then, Keisuke...
--...please let me race the Eight-Six.
"What?
This isn't Akagi or his home course,
so this is as fair as it gets.
--Hey.
--lketani.
Who is he'!
--No idea.
--Kenta!
Takumi Fujiwara, isn't it'!
Kenta Nakamura of the Red Suns.
How about me and you in this rain'!
We gotta talk to my brother first.
Let's ask the spectators, Keisuke.
Wanna see us battle it out in the rain?!
--Yeah!
--Come on!
--Darn.
--Hard to say no now.
But he's racing against
Ryosuke Takahashi next week.
I'm first.
If you can't beat me, you're
certainly not worth Ryosuke': time.
What do you say'!
I love racing in the rain.
Don't tell me you're scared of the rain'!
No, not now!
He hasn't, uh, been himself lately.
Sure, why not'!
Wow,
--Hold it.
--No one can stop it now.
--But...
--He's not anyone': "private" target.
Every racer wants a piece of him.
I know you understand that feeling.
That's more like it.
Downhill in the rain.
That makes it a pure skill race.
Set your proud Eight-Six next to mine.
--Let's go, ltsuki.
--I'm going, too'!
If I leave you here, I'll have
to come back up afterwards.
Let's just race down and go straight home.
So, I'm getting in, then'!
Wait, ltsuki, do you mind sitting in the back'!
In the back'! Okay, I guess.
Is this a strategy?
Maybe it is... maybe it isn't.
What'! You don't know yourself?
How do I stay seated when you drift?
--You'll manage.
--What'!! Hey!
It's only from here to the
bottom of the mountain.
It's not over.There's one more race.
I hear Akina': Eight-Six is racing!
No oncoming traffic!
Let's do this!
I wasn't expecting this.
Yeah. But there's nothing we can do now.
Don't worry, Keisuke.
Ilike rain.
Before I joined the team,
I purposely waited for rainy days
to practice my drifting technique.
The rain reduces the wear on the tires.
I see you're confident,
but don't take it lightly.
I'm the most experienced in the rain.
I know I'm better than him in the rain,
because the rain is on my side.
Takumi, you don't look too sharp.
Are you sure you'll be okay in the rain'!
Who knows'!
I can't go too fast in the rain,
so I'll drive normally.
Who knows if I'll be fast or slow'!
I'll take it easy,
'cause if I crashed, my dad would kill me.
That's true.
Bu! if he loses this race,
there won't be a race against...
...Ryosuke Takahashi!
I'll count down!
Five... Four...
Three... Two...
One... Go!
Ouch!
This isn't... normal!
Ai ni tsukare hate samayotteta koro
Yokubou duke ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure nu unmeiwa
Mujaki nu hitomi ni miserarete yuku
Sake bum no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku kimi o daite
Talia hitotsu kono omoi o shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi o kanadeyou...
Kagayaku mirai e
Kazoe kirenai hodo tashikame aou
Jounetsu yo eien e todoke
Sake bum no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani o ushinattemo
kono ude o hanasanai
Utsukushiku karen ni sake...
Kiseki no hana yo
You seem confident in the min, Kentu.
Yes, I am confident.
H! win because Keisuke is watching me.
But even Keisuke lost to this Eight-Six.
Pm avenging that loss! This is for Keisuke.
"This is your first time here...
--No problem!
I have to give it my best for Keisuke!
Kama, do you have feelings for Keisuke?
I, uh...
Next on initial D: "The Rainy Downhill."
Don'! miss it!