"This story is fiction. All names of characters, places and organizations
in the story are fictional. Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Kikanaku natteta
ano CD wo mam sagasou
ltsushika nervous-gachi no futari no tame ni
Speed tozashita kako ga
mezamete iku melody
Chikyuu ga furueru hodo ni
kakushinhan no neraiuchi
Blazin' beat
Hui hodo tsuyoi ai wo abisete
Sakebu kaze hibiku oto de daite
Naked mind, desire
Motomeru koto ni tsumi wa naku
Utagau koto sum wasurete mi wo makasete
Blazin' beat! Yo! Binbin de ikou,
moral wa hashotte ii darou
Shoudo no mama ni tobidasou
Weekend da yo zenin shugo!
M.O.V.E., move, buchigiri hajikeru
Torihada mon no wakuwaku
wo sagasou, it's the time!
"Act 2: Team Emperor on Akina!"
I can'! lose this race!
I refuse to lose to those who
enter my turf with dirty shoes!
It's time to go.
What?!
No way! He passed Takeshi easily.
That Evo IV is good!
Takeshi': R32 fell behind.
The Evo IV seems to be pulling away.
What them'!
What the heck is that Ian-Evo thinking?
Against a skilled Myogi racer,
he chose to be in front, which is unfavorable.
Confidence?
Or is he just an idiot?
This race is just starting!
Big brother, are you in there?
What is it, Keisuke'!
The Ian-Evo team is racing at Mt. Myogi.
I just got the news.
Against the Night Kids' Nakazato'!
I suppose.
Who's going to win, big brother?
Just this once, I'm rooting for Nakazato to win.
The Len-Eve's vulgar spoiler
makes me want to puke.
Nakazato': strength lies in his boldness
and his offensive driving method.
When he's on, he's fast,
but he tends to crack under pressure.
I sure hope he's recovered
from the loss he suffered against you.
This isn't happening!
But the race is far from over!
If! don't stop them...
...who will?!
Damn it!
We get your team sticker, as promised.
In no time, my Evo lV's spoiler will be covered
with the torn stickers of
all the teams in Gunma.
Don't start celebrating yet!
There are many fast racers in Gunma!
That sounds to me like
the pathetic cry of a loser.
--Let's go, Seiji.
--Yeah.
By the way...
...from now on, you pull
over whenever you see
a car with the Emperor sticker on it.
Takeshi... I still can't believe he was
faster than you in an uphill battle.
The Ian-Evo team defeated the Night Kids.
What'! Seriously?
That's all anyone': talking about this morning.
Nakazato': R32 crashed into a wall
and suffered severe damage.
That's tragic.
Things have been rough
for the Night Kids lately.
I feel bad for them.
I heard that the Ian-Evo squad is planning
to conquer Gunma within a month.
I'm sure they'll come to Akina, too.
What do we do if they come here?!
We have no choice but to face them.
We're Akina': team, so if they challenge us,
I have no intention of running away.
I've already switched my 513's tires
to ones with better grip.
I informed the team members already.
Thank you very much.
Takumi.
They may specifically challenge
you to a downhill battle,
but you can just ignore them.
Your undefeated streak is our pride.
I'd hate to ruin it against a Ian-Evo.
You're not officially a Speed Star, either.
I want you to keep winning, too.
The Ian-Evo is no joke.
It's like racing against a WRC rally car.
Its light body is equipped
with turbo and 4WD.
It has no real weaknesses.
That car shouldn't be allowed on any pass.
I hate to...
I hate to avoid a race.
I want to race them, too.
Takumi, you sound like a true racer now!
You're my true friend! I love it!
I'm positive you'll win!
The Ian-Evo is going down!
Is that wise'!
Right now, his chance of winning is...
...zero percent.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Upgrading the Eight-Six'!
That came out of nowhere, Yuichi.
I'm sure it's crossed your mind.
Since Takumi is evolving into a fine racer,
I feel like it's about time to upgrade
the Eight-Six': capabilities to match his needs.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not telling you what to do.
I just want to know your plans.
I guess this engine is getting old,
and it's about time to overhaul it.
Yeah.
Actually...
...I have one already.
What'!
Is that true'!
Yeah, I happened to get an incredible thing
from an unlikely source.
An incredible thing?
All right, I'll show it to you. Get in the car.
You'll get chills.
"Suzuki Motors"
This is incredible!This is gold!
You got chills, didn't you'!
More than that. It blew me away!
How did you manage to get this'!
I'm already psyched about the
idea of this in the Eight-Six.
Me, too.
I haven't felt this excited in a while.
It's almost too good forTakumi, isn't it'!
When are you putting it in'!
We'll see.
A better engine won't
automatically make the car better.
I'll need to adjust many things
and fine-tune the "footwork."
With the right balance,
it'll be an incredible machine.
I'll test it myself and come up
with the best configuration.
I'll need your help then, Masashi.
No problem, but you're so darn stubborn.
You never compromise.
This is like the old days.
But there is one more thing
Takumi hasn't accomplished in that car.
What is that'!
Nothing, really.
Stop teasing and tell us.
I'll tell you, but you have to promise me
not to tell Takumi about this.
We won't tell him.
Then I'll tell you.
That one thing is...
...losing a race.
What do you mean'!
Takumi has tried so hard
to remain undefeated.
That's what I don't like.
As long as he's winning,
he won't have a true
appreciation for this upgrade.
He needs to push the car's
capabilities to the very limit
and find out that it's still
not good enough to win.
There's a lesson to be learned
in that humiliation.
Until he loses...
...I can't upgrade the Eight-Six.
At this rate,
the side of the spoiler
will be covered in no time.
It's kind of fun if I think of it as a game.
But I wanna race more capable racers.
Where's our next target, Kyoichi'!
Tomorrow night, we'll head to Akina.
Akina': Eight-Six... how boring!
I don't mind doing it myself, Seiji.
What'!
Kyoichi will race him'! Why'!
I don't know.
Our ultimate target...
...is Ryosuke Takahashi of the Akagi Red Suns.
But before that, we'll defeat Akina': Eight-Six.
I went to see the course yesterday.
The slope is severe.
My Evo Ill is lighter and better suited for it.
You kidding me'! Let me take him, Kyoichi.
No matter where I race, I won't lose to anyone.
There is only one car that
my Evo IV can't beat, Kyoichi.
It's your Evo Ill.
Team Emperor's ace is not
needed against an Eight-Six.
I'll do it.
What's this'!
"Do you know that Natsuki Mogi
is dating an older man
in a Mercedes for money?"
"...Natsuki Mogi..."
"...dating..."
Takumi!
--Ready to go'!
--Yeah.
What do you have there?
It's nothing.
Hey,Takumi'!
This car magazine I bought recently
has a feature article on the Evo IV,
so maybe you should read it.
You may be battling against one.
No, thanks.
Why'! I'm sure it'll be very helpful.
I probably wouldn't know what to do
with the knowledge after reading the article.
How can I drive the Eight-Six faster'!
That's all I think about.
It doesn't matter which car I go up against.
Haven't you ever considered getting
a more powerful engine or something?
Not really.
Seriously? I'm dying for more
power for my Eight-Five!
A more powerful engine...
I have no clue.
--Takumi!
"What's going on, lketani'!
They're coming to Akina.
Tonight.
Here comes the Ian-Evo squad!
This will be an incredible battle.
Here they come! The Ian-Evo squad!
That white Evo IV in front must be the one
that defeated Nakazato in Myogi.
Rumor has it that he's ridiculously fast.
I knew it! The guys I met at Akina Lake!
So you're the Speed Stars.
I'm Sudo, the leader of Team Emperor.
I'm sure you already know
that we have only one demand.
A downhill race against your Eight-Six.
That's all.
We'll accept all your demands.
Any number of races, of any type,
under any conditions.
But if you fail to win even one race,
we'll take your team sticker. Understood?
Our sticker?
--What are they gonna do with it'!
--No idea.
--It's okay, right'!
--We accept.
Then let's get right to the race.
We don't have much time.
The first race is the main downhill race.
Have your Eight-Six ready.
Who's racing for you'!
I am, and I drive an Evo IV.
Iketani, they said they were
ready for more than one race...
...so who's racing after Takumi'!
IfTakumi loses, I'll race next.
If he can beat Takumi, I sure
won't be able to beat him...
...but we can't accept defeat without a fight.
Then I'll race after you.
We've been relying on Takumi too much lately.
Let's show him that we're capable, too!
Yeah!
I'm counting on you, our leadoff man!
Go get him!
Here comes Fujiwara Tofu Shop!
The Eight-Six vs. the Evo IV!
Good luck, Gunma': downhill hero!
Don't take this lightly, Seiji.
Go with "Simulation 3."
What'! Are you serious?
"Simulation 3" against an Eight-Six'!
That's right.
I can tell. I felt his energy.
This Eight-Six is capable. He': not a fake.
He has something that
made him defeat Ryosuke.
Until we know what it is,
we can't let our guard down.
I'll count down.
No, no need for that.
This is a race, not a time trial.
The one with less engine power
can start whenever he likes.
The other starts accordingly.
We'll start late,
but that's our handicap for
having more horsepower.
We call it the "Handicap Method."
What do you say'!
If it's okay with you, Takumi.
I saw him once by Akina Lake.
It never occurred to me
that a young kid like him
was the driver of Akina': Eight-Six.
Kyoichi has developed three strategies to win
on an opponent': course.
"Simulation 3" is only used
against the toughest opponents,
so why use it against this Eight-Six?
I don'! get it.
Takumi zoomed out!
Go,Takumi!
I won't show you how great the Evo IV is...
...but how incredible I am!
Furikaereba itsudatte
Kawaranu kimi no egao ga aim
Arukitsukare tachidomaru hi mo
Chiisa nu yorokobi no hi mo
Kono ryoute ni kakaekirenai
Al' wo oshiete kureta
Atatakaku
Sotto yasashiku yomigaeru kaze wa
{ma hitori sora wo
Mitsumeteru boku ni hohoendeiru
Mada ano hi no mama no
Mabushisa de te wo futteiru
Kimi wa everlasting memory
The race has begun!
Does Seiji understand the reason
for using "Simulation 3"?
Next on initial D: Second Stage...
"Premonition of Defeat."
Don'! miss it!